[{"topicId":"7","id":"7000","langCode":"en","question":"REy4vdSgrCZ2uHF5HKOIsUSjPXwALCzGnOuA40Sl57+MtYlP4AOLl1xh3d8dtwz/7uEpX/GIKmvIpjVCCjm2gg\u003d\u003d","answers":["at","on ","behind","between"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"Es15p0wqWvHqNtb/OLWsRNdndwwzSl0gJqwtWYn4iAMLrwnIEUUirDsHOCY2xHxGc1k62q+RukhOCBOG80D6Vchnzs0ani4drambS+x7eb7d3ooJSIRySoemm+NmVGvHx35FShcXxX/mHNHVbYGlFSwRdLJeqlEd60LOFsXPGu8BlNsrxVWB2WcVq4WXHnMy+YF+0h6Yv4gyCaroDof9f4wlaM5fsv34n4HbxRsTbwMo1d9diZNBl9ZYZ23F7EDHrvbp0Z+ssigbNWV2qA11APue8W2WU6noRamwbuKd3b54sE0DXgXqXNrcZrujzsauYOByInKFev6fpPK2Cb0kMjYc/RvuR8fTUHeRL7CYXLLRdPzcJEtQCeh0vBTI/NBj/5XR5TOObR9PIwRntXztNJwgeiT40eZXTaw8uwjG0lE4nFn4qijp6tAX/mEesbBDkQmwSA6xPUB7cral/EnHaYe5qoQxIA88Zp/9BRNqrs0czQHYDs0H/wGfsWEW/nHc2nhdgC5i5DfN589yASjDLT0Mo3D1t/pYPOlnf56FwvD0WSFQFEcVujMoz6q1fJgkD+CUo2yvmrVlnbWfb8IeOQc6Mj42ZqfqD2p1SCeN7dq0GcIIzDeq1rQdOGbdeZ/pntN6Xqa+zxCneyHMgtEiiv8f7q4T7evI8EKEhpVCwl12JJGqnX7zNE385op4BoltSjLBitsOOF+Xbgyzvc/yh6hVhtIB9aXVtbWJbmCJZAFZJZFnRmkwszRMWOVSU2CZl3HtHH5i/o1unXpYmQpi+eWZE5+fOwUchQg1Pw68pAfAYgiV+iYmEL2mkf9vCJV9DqkyTtoTwYj7R6P1kLFC5gcUPRNg3QE5q/hNmlOElv4\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7001","langCode":"en","question":"bV8rYTwM6z95cijcqoaLFRXwMMFvJ6EflXj5ERv0AhSHVBylAbkZqfzxLUo+rXClG5Z+IxKUeLrUUXoQGeFr+g\u003d\u003d","answers":["after","along","opposite","in"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"Zuw9XipiFvsCiutiuKLogpXR4M/KxxjyggTVjjRHoGOc9AEsrVwFpxw8CO0Pu3rKi4wATSPEVIiaJLjjcNwXzmk9UUjOt+jpgb2OFAiQJJ01AbjuE5Ud7+Pi2Nq8hcfefRfsZqc0pykv/6ZQn903vPnyf9tt9SNsrsCbRb2FWSLiSNNvWcsXD8s5tXpE+YNCykKPK8hyfONtOILxd/zDS7B1IO3k5CYplq4HehR6CNTGFyUo1aYY90w3txQola4yI+uC4x4jfoO1Ybt+SNkruhqxJP56P7PMv4ekItGvV83oF85nAuObk9apwgspr41+bXaNpVF/8uk7raFIU4HEOUDhnJw1x6WViYjLDrYbDu2bloerpkem6GPEU+Cz9s7jimQ3o8CWU4ALB4mDNvoyVHSlMcKLE1L8j/HQTdO5ZWbpmDm/XHk1jaHxZ4TL3u5qheEEc7dbnn0kaXIwp8Ll4iQh9TDwc3z7MAtCfvYNtxc73TAsbNm9NmBCHqdkQko8WqvsbwUs8wkrfW9NsHWNbqw+EV4sByl20/6fjGxTMSt5vKuqksCXE2aDf98TjuSBmQ49c3259Y8i4qHcWgHpV1i3OfgdVj+Vxz7J5KE95NjthzR5BAV1MyIgF1BgCGNwgBH8CMHB3jSv9wtbwB3j9IdeXzFaAABe/ASEer8HJT+MmKx9Jlz3usnFUVyzF7Bdr2jJYNLvA6OBCXjMsofsHPzlTuJ9Ulu5DX0qMwuMyR5pdAtMRwSrMETC+UST2+GlLjuFdj1bewOEca8ed8f2JQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7002","langCode":"en","question":"PUkftUcRH004UQVaiCxjHh/7jTwwG84vE6/2eBndw9za4TXkhIGIuVoQ8ucWR+8UYQVOP8sCHOEJ9Zqpn5+eYA\u003d\u003d","answers":["into","during","at","in"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"Zuw9XipiFvsCiutiuKLogpXR4M/KxxjyggTVjjRHoGOc9AEsrVwFpxw8CO0Pu3rKi4wATSPEVIiaJLjjcNwXzmk9UUjOt+jpgb2OFAiQJJ01AbjuE5Ud7+Pi2Nq8hcfefRfsZqc0pykv/6ZQn903vPnyf9tt9SNsrsCbRb2FWSLiSNNvWcsXD8s5tXpE+YNCykKPK8hyfONtOILxd/zDS7B1IO3k5CYplq4HehR6CNTGFyUo1aYY90w3txQola4yI+uC4x4jfoO1Ybt+SNkruhqxJP56P7PMv4ekItGvV83oF85nAuObk9apwgspr41+bXaNpVF/8uk7raFIU4HEOUDhnJw1x6WViYjLDrYbDu2ga3sH7u8Tehbe1+WEgdGUCf84ZzGOe+Xo3+clXm0Ns9rciEVb8HR/oRMxGq4ovlq351xJZkI6Fh4JR9A3B8E0AA+XhgEc3baL9GvsPHNMJ+8W2UYyw6n2URpTpaLojuRt306Agxp9r5dTxxYlqOJryl68XXp+OxtENvqf9PUBci62XpSzM+0FzSwM//y71d8y2SKGfznoL0RfacpaLJf2RR6igVU7Y90aOBVdspOZ+9E5NisZn/1ixNGidx3nXIu+bldPXuJWj+YgiukxsyX6L6VAkF0So/BirwAK8zXjcp5RI4cL04xXZHJgkmz6JEpBCukzobq4REBHmv3W+dNqCAVXnjQh+2MOgMMFwn+q9hrV1Naj1ZjlrA4svIZDAqQH1JoClxzSs3GbHvjPPVB5ppdNbIPFGsxpHRgA/P78pRLotqh7Z1p4nJqkuSN90aV6oyEZuSs3otMvJnLKOEhaQZR8Jr5LzONhNpy9tom4n8Y/3eSjRqV76huGkcyowve1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7003","langCode":"en","question":"Va1WYNy5IXBKuwtvu4mJibsoPDZ/1QWyR653OlMf+F9thqTCd68uyGFNrKsmWeDS","answers":["at","on","in","for"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"Zuw9XipiFvsCiutiuKLogpXR4M/KxxjyggTVjjRHoGOc9AEsrVwFpxw8CO0Pu3rKi4wATSPEVIiaJLjjcNwXzmk9UUjOt+jpgb2OFAiQJJ01AbjuE5Ud7+Pi2Nq8hcfefRfsZqc0pykv/6ZQn903vPnyf9tt9SNsrsCbRb2FWSLiSNNvWcsXD8s5tXpE+YNCykKPK8hyfONtOILxd/zDS7B1IO3k5CYplq4HehR6CNTGFyUo1aYY90w3txQola4yI+uC4x4jfoO1Ybt+SNkruhqxJP56P7PMv4ekItGvV83oF85nAuObk9apwgspr41+bXaNpVF/8uk7raFIU4HEOUDhnJw1x6WViYjLDrYbDu3+907V9Ur+XdfqeMN2DyaMsnl+zjjnkV9nYoilwLoZntkcwetBTJENcP4MIp94/GxIdCFPPUlnhrgQUw6UrdoSqhIdHgGi4GGQjWqY9Uj3B0m9mLS1v8VQJADnBz8e2LrjXLpwpb66uF2AxSIlKFA2+jX/YAkkfMJ0dq3AwClvS2XVhbx7WhG9yOOj++qRFLmkjYD2V+uZjR+9kQZKviKyhBRShv0qYV3MMGpck4tn9PqTuC0ptqHVlh9r8RI2g2nDdBYcQhxsohw7aFkocISQGGBtxNqOOPTD1y+NHDla6c3gyeevI4RyBXlsaH56qIQ6vGsEtezOgNTkmI0UjNuQa/V4aYNPEx8XQi7R+VcOvH5F90bCODZznvZ9zYfNj5TO6IFVuZ5prq0bJmA2F/RNnNMR3KLG6eCBc63ff+u0FiMSgyUaB5SRVO9a9MMmDLUlQ2KTvLsDTe3bbXXtHfKHLk57fyS2EY6vRhBKVSThOxoR6FeRGrq/ncWxWgYCSXdtkUJYFO/ztqXZeL/l+UplvRS/ZAaCPr+njjw0gbKF+fr20p1s/00BZNhqwBiuX6JTy0+AaQVGsLpptn1XaAV807/LuFsTCvWVIfqufJ6es8NEqGji+vkBCHG8jzNz5vpKXexacEP6OCoH9/vDZd/zZ6Oh37e7zYs2uIoZ0wiOBE/bldjNcUXtWBdiZtepQ7PjFwu5rUUXWqqw1wvGsPuIQT4IFGmSC4dQFeSGYKXY0zbeDloPlfKLs123ipYwyKtXIzRzA7a2M57g8H4lGI/bksYpyc86/xgBs+YJ3wsrvq726dGfrLIoGzVldqgNdQDqXQ66QFtNC+HZXglIZXCJL+ihX/mEK6cHnD1jY3xk1OnrZsWFAFKSEhaMJW2L7tNA2qz82htPx96yd2oPaLhggFaqphTeH9a6i4nL82vx/f6s1sUCGDPODa0hlOKorXs\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7004","langCode":"en","question":"eKJ08tYWEDqlm2/hOHenONBP2LoPzSluuBTXoZ56WcxUOxPOR+3mi1maCuDKyfhMinQx2ijC4/ouJbP/qqekGg\u003d\u003d","answers":["with","after","on","among"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"qlHqgDxi0Hp0QWfRJti4OZ7MdV1YBP4zGW6kxw5JAaoJcjDtqKs3tkV4cg3PP8+sy+d8qEqlIyZgsmiEEx+u1eNBhnVc/wRs8J6ntSxm0K3NYhOrA+JmLX8QNjLxepj0GKMjJdsFBxvZC2+2Rc7nRgYXRHpWcGrW0ECzAyBrv35Vt0s24Al1mIyxU0Scqlb/MtGM5An+xMbviDvwEHNHtGHlee86kizLs4nRPTNVIReoYgz7PMtWWK4aOt21griBUfScgXoyyzOdkWS1jxq7oVhWtSmz3I+khYuM1gJHsvdEotTrXJP1C1USmbHYd+wxPLQLYjSnetYfXppEJkyGv/TfFcSiKwzblLyjcla+glAGmhMDhs91P332rPLJWivcEatqag/jd74qLCUf2tW2ax55eBHLaj38a19ArmTA4oi943EQlCeGGfshSoiJL5hbGOMrXLHtEOmgMhDx9OLYqL1tkiJhlC07UuAlqXA9iCbPOOLoD3Adcm+CZLSduMVnGOMrXLHtEOmgMhDx9OLYqBD2Nf6ZEO+HO9n/5ObF3Nkj9rOv+sOXr8yRxkzCOGp7HYEEcKesQy/y/NBCCznmkudeqde4g4YaoHupLmbDJryOp7td92z9/4iOOn2opNs5zuz8WVvMEfP92GrLdkVOrh6cG1tlBXEnxH4gd+fWx9pohDiYeOWWJDsk2PkW6n5go1BLuJyGblz1G/YQrTBYOINzUKM+XXJspGx95NNS3g1Qnog8HOog8u7pw46y2x1v4Dz/bbQC9VmrfY4w3HvjDCjhhOIdLxX2MbmQkLnfOJa06esMYHyXlFoBAx5Ge4cdh7c3oaNP4ovZ4IMWCfK1QA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7005","langCode":"en","question":"R/+bv8WQQv/6tqVa7vhDXQHBpJEwo4GHbi/cPfLkj1dUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["above","before","until","during"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"jxxzVCM1tnxzeF65d5zNjR2B/Ef8tASh6LDRJyRcSkHJyTDbo167MSPi68H3AghCJfxtvhApUYeFpcW3OBt4/dBPuV40RElm20NH3XCqej6pAVuhbeTakRFHtlLgJwbnuC8JL+Tz4gLwyHoNcAEXqOowXDGy7dB94C0rzX3xO5k8jQt/bInEjBQ8rvSiZ6darGxlXloFUYmRI6Xh/2PwTVcKHojgJsAdYYQd/W00YrAlzZ6IMdetQrvxr3PX9qTFFBx7GQWO54eIHIBXpffQ6f+dgKcNSFjYhOfkdOq3ihslGyhOCEQ8L+eHoxon9hyvNl7vqu6CWd/E6wkBlMikyFjmBpSiWPvI/DCgiqOJ7R7PqlJ7rA6odPUgnKsHXJyK6u3lSXFk99kt886k6liP3SRkIIPq4+wyBWxWLwuzDPwdF9f7pFW3P3qJFYmPvERRZEdNQypVl8uA3fkUInKza85uN7Uf3qyXM1Olr3ks6JevUJFx/Swp63zWa1OEjzvq0LiyTL0lttJdK193sJpONngyTUDSMBxg8WiYGyIjqNjPGeXy6ld/uJr95DqcZd0T4dMV2xWfPWsYXo7SOKAjqBnTU+FZaUyHU3FCc7j7ik3tHg+eyHmrapGtNOhFS+Jn6IzHmbFK/fIyepoFP6OS6ztRCTiyI2PsH5BJ+Y3bEQgVxns5yDo8m1Z35t3yrD03CUolR1SMXHzshhzWr2dGX19qXBrWs/qBx9/ryplHj3VYMZ9q0lAFIyEHHomwtCPRQPutFBrpEv8OEmmzUN5Ivg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7006","langCode":"en","question":"tR6fOZp4rEWpukJUtRs8BtboG//1EhSjZncy3jQrUdD3jZG2N3GNdlHWHjSVbtF3hG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["inside","below","along","behind"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"zcT5P4XkdYF0B6Jn3ytxFsykB5Aqnwra2xO6QRFLFsJ9NcwZo/v2PufBT0lZTYZ0rA7Lm9+EwsZfUZTdh9mc0PdL7KFRvMKI3u+fKAY7xvckgNNTrpPDHq0E2VB9EKdpE6TF1czs24e17ZiN22qtoxEN9q+qApk5I4ne1+9386NOpazEbr3s3stVsZnyhc2+WD8fvGsVXldVzj5cLmtvwjKIwKgZV6b25dDYCuf9bQk2GJrgtSe+EuLCq3CTTvTgj60Gg2iQ/N+/ug8easuzVtNvuy1Yzb5sWIdhtBkbHUAJd3BczdpUeZHdiDlh60ux09PFuQ8LW0ivOyyE53lD2vw6Qa3KES+Mar6tQWr5XhyE5UYnCJxqxdHkRviO/Ll/oUv08xeNTXP67NiCt83l2Kj/ByqtN/QuOJUP/8AgKCFJKhaPe6D2g8k5a9tHNFCDGh3pM0+hTSryakMKRFxbzuIyVjGrJdXZEBvpJXVZNMPJIxZSahnLqQ2u/jppCFzF"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7007","langCode":"en","question":"fhsVZH5Q0yjSg4J2tL4EzghqpEaX9a1Mg4bXkDd7+9UecDL+KEc5C4r3kx0zf2cda8rt7ewhGGsh+oQThxobgA\u003d\u003d","answers":["by","near","beside","across"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"Osvykcw0EfbL0RTsVL6PMfsu1cb00EwsZQsHYEZoMQfikE7eVqae9K7Z/NscBfY2WBE3vEUX+Su4BmECSNJIyGJhoDGGcgdpR/CW/aI4ZU7DQrTuZeK0rkqwy9dcN4Ugc4LfoW7UgftmGqP9Z13B+4ar1D5kjMBYDTDXHkDbna0m0RHPIPQ7EmPOLTBla4lxbOgioFzlzYdLVuR8kOdZHXTcpGYMq3GJAWOMYpalvKTZNg9/diUWsi4SeDQDcB0wqJhCAXc9IpIUGvhd/0vHcS9AH5VljOwtbezb3kunez7U8JS5muw3St/jbGv9t0IUQf2/nALp9L5SjaIuTjAMz7ZSLoMI/uu9cZMT361PIEF6FAHSoEJkBGR3sTnkpF4WQwysbeuvvFYDMZodLzGRFN2oQ1KLc9lKusakYSV6AdfJ0xSW+CMrqSfHVZa0K9YPM+Ey04fwPRwaM1nxPV+ddMztPPEHaHW9/NEnKc01wYKzD+UT/QGBNWyv1oru98KL3rnwYP9KDAJCfxe1o1q4Ug\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7008","langCode":"en","question":"gZPaucJjrUoAoct2zDwcVajGLNt31Zi3l6qFgvPw9fjJWzifvR3OX0adeLaUX53A/fixW0ZWCDUkO40CkzgqphjFkpid2EGQwy9rOEWUGu35iY2f3UxI1mGxSoVZ7x3F","answers":["until ","to","by","with"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"EZl3UQZ9WafJb9mAujcEDQju4oOFduhf+NLc/5ekCzQ08K5kgLDTKgpKUoWLt8gfUFg+Q0z7gcw6zBsm4Ndph+p1LaHIOtODD45nCMLKq1/6E9XGIiLlatA+5ooRk9hnHJTlAHllpmfxq7SDrHl15tAWVTZNvw7Q2NO+uK0ySpXqSumceK89TLBFkb999P/udIiQfk1AqOMKvqYvNfaHG/rwaIJ9z5wdFCRbq9HB2gtnghGkY6bAfVz3aVWfHPQdJGFb4xoGA2JXBJkJrc6fMSHQYrhzOwSa6mScuz/zlJk+CaymqU59BHwYM4goWCCsDEsCo1cxugcicJLiB9afPxF2fRyACwd07GUAEjtUUPvZYBncmLxxoGElHz4IhfuUc4j21At2gWHKqiHJNY7PP/su1cb00EwsZQsHYEZoMQfikE7eVqae9K7Z/NscBfY2WBE3vEUX+Su4BmECSNJIyGJhoDGGcgdpR/CW/aI4ZU7DQrTuZeK0rkqwy9dcN4UgJuexB6TKB9jiBUGcAvV1fLR791hI5moqun/E2S4G2lbozAeNZnoC9cscl2VQMmuFtFY7V+gJc3WZbu7suCe+i4GMKD7fqslq8PnvsfgOxwD3+bXDKoikHnoatnMgXK/KJzKTWcmqWl9dTJkVxFgd58pijHWYyN1LNzmyV7m/ZJChPHWtc696fVJK8tg/aqKwIrYva0L9OZRh1nmmA3Ohkg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7009","langCode":"en","question":"3wPeR7k+d1e/PSgVQHKvZDHh8wrmUQ/sTa8hcvWrqYVektzgVHs8SzGdrQ/WPWdMZFZh6fqsfRbXbRA2mMFtAw\u003d\u003d","answers":["among","under","over","across"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"o3EGj872o2mcxGsP85LHHqSOofXkmpMFhjdV9SCvK1rbcpSSxYQCmVKuiDZGuyQdqjulvYE+65WMGAvMI/LUvyRSuX+AmmHtCAr+WK3zGU/NUY4PomaVuXuVmAOEDVT2VhfpMvL1Y4uuIU6590FmyZFJUeDgtAVKEu9IfjEmR+3ueymHOh4GuekM+dNfvmpUL7KF5V5YB9oufo+AVzy6Ovekt/BVPGbIv09FvJBSKfpaHSN86mJheQlBZQ8zVeLqgkiDf1di6oofc+PDSdZ7VC6cQn03Xqo2gJmtaHGJ9eZXD84EXe+30x5Mj8MSw6tmbYvc1pQlHTAZ+/2Zq/tX1ad6Dowx1I0aREwCenF+jJ09RH8UCvJDd5WMnlebfRQXhruC9KsYLrmshQJVtGjROiqVCr/hcOQ2HbNdBr8XfX95If87hjXalUzZC25eXjlhJinzZ6TfcUE7WjP+QugMRV0Ww0PLP/u2Tq0PmNXjSJkLt/pEj8UqSGIiUjMp10OeZwkNvdziiKhD0iXIiuWIYLBkzw0eTfGu13DLtCAdV6wLt/pEj8UqSGIiUjMp10OeZwkNvdziiKhD0iXIiuWIYK9jJ+BVd03lkgutydnVChlCUqAA0M5xCLa4Vdg+HLlsqjulvYE+65WMGAvMI/LUv6Tesza8J9T+gAcuSNL+UqWk3yNj1L3O2xG/HU86USNhkV0xseWOb1q+sUD59J7O4tuEv96Wx6bAR4XWvZQ8R5/0jlt+BwZ0ENfeexCJwA1ottExNXruBp0TFX8G3VuJK2ZjUtirzGcgNsTT4OIovEwOqTJO2hPBiPtHo/WQsULmKZlP3Itx5fJTQG/+De3CPA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7010","langCode":"en","question":"oULUFiddDM6UTdjW9jIE5fAJXKNTOXM+Rg35lQ8zN3VwEPy+z1+9UfEH8IhjRbhLfPTCyeIUIbopiCyzuQmAEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["since","by","at","in"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"Zuw9XipiFvsCiutiuKLogpXR4M/KxxjyggTVjjRHoGOc9AEsrVwFpxw8CO0Pu3rKi4wATSPEVIiaJLjjcNwXzmk9UUjOt+jpgb2OFAiQJJ01AbjuE5Ud7+Pi2Nq8hcfefRfsZqc0pykv/6ZQn903vPnyf9tt9SNsrsCbRb2FWSLiSNNvWcsXD8s5tXpE+YNCykKPK8hyfONtOILxd/zDS7B1IO3k5CYplq4HehR6CNTGFyUo1aYY90w3txQola4yI+uC4x4jfoO1Ybt+SNkruhqxJP56P7PMv4ekItGvV83oF85nAuObk9apwgspr41+bXaNpVF/8uk7raFIU4HEOUDhnJw1x6WViYjLDrYbDu1qhkm0xNC1c9BcA73xtuZRYBE+9d0v6Ll8lvMKIT4ndMpzXcf6dMMWXmThQrV14Q8zaFqgjeTOOnZrzxjeMaNl6Nl0QjowtYqQagam2wZEXkq6CZQcwjt+wN8iArNnZqcQO8aYr5RxmF33PwN7na68ZFvQDAa5OQnXlPwzWCeGgPTfFcSiKwzblLyjcla+glCywSnPGdSG4JDKiBxgMIxnMsceewCK3kQVu8aZeVPKqRDl/AiYS1GXf7J3n7jBg/Wc9yraYZ3+Yes0Rr31Lq6/8m11PKiEqxKKrCulyePG/0NpBsCwtlcGkaj6gcD4DWPlM2VldL/cPy0AqCDonH+ULBpupT/fjR6QEmI7mtpbfW6nPQD0pvKnbqdo4/P4s9FblnW7CHRS5Yakl3yrHJIZHH9Mhl0km8VQo3ReToYAeIkFg77+p2+nXNiWHpTXZrICs+QsrE/Zk8CbW7BqD+YQ9f6Lg4y4zc/KHU2FagJ4Evxn8llGc67MFp/vmrtPTtTL8MeTkDWPkLdSdWiU0DK5QZR8Jr5LzONhNpy9tom4n8Y/3eSjRqV76huGkcyowvfamEFhq0A5S8PVu2CMjEBn"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7011","langCode":"en","question":"xukWGiXn8xZacXJcdNA5FD6UM4Nm4rhpFmmA+HyqLJCGoLgUw1wsnSyJ2R9Mys6S3s2tv4jlyamsCUbZof9hToRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["on","for","in","after"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"qlHqgDxi0Hp0QWfRJti4OZ7MdV1YBP4zGW6kxw5JAaoJcjDtqKs3tkV4cg3PP8+sy+d8qEqlIyZgsmiEEx+u1eNBhnVc/wRs8J6ntSxm0K3NYhOrA+JmLX8QNjLxepj0GKMjJdsFBxvZC2+2Rc7nRgYXRHpWcGrW0ECzAyBrv35Vt0s24Al1mIyxU0Scqlb/MtGM5An+xMbviDvwEHNHtGHlee86kizLs4nRPTNVIReoYgz7PMtWWK4aOt21griBUfScgXoyyzOdkWS1jxq7oVhWtSmz3I+khYuM1gJHsvdEotTrXJP1C1USmbHYd+wxPLQLYjSnetYfXppEJkyGv/TfFcSiKwzblLyjcla+glAGmhMDhs91P332rPLJWivcEatqag/jd74qLCUf2tW2ax55eBHLaj38a19ArmTA4oijPsG4Z99Dx4yh43pQ7YfCPICpGNj4IH7oe+TfbjYZemZcKCR+SN24xK3uyUAcm0f/yZRZ4pIq0IdlajFD5Vxx4X1HN8Bt7KQilqCepJYvQJsh5lizzehcLXMZhqKIwwgTmjDLRJ7AT85AMPG4IthVLKGgjzn6ln+uwrBqKbrfpwsOoo4yabOq6PLoMk4a1sJqiUNAZrOEIQMfAUXERHN7HFwcxxs1F3OMj0pgbqOELr4wnt3nhTsspGz7n3fESu6bCqEnbRTBAb2TFArqWMm7+1OdXPrakpFpjVxflnAr/njQA5vnU5TwQyZaqM9+d2GtcY/vtJbyL00sJ/D+ZIP3bUOF0dWeXO5kSxXkZMjzzsF+k04CE04eoKwpe51F1iECv359PIMIjtzqNV6ZM2yeFS4FoKyl4qXuXahKqRo8t7NCgz9N/TBhQ31wi0hX6byyeX7OOOeRX2diiKXAuhme2RzB60FMkQ1w/gwin3j8bEh0IU89SWeGuBBTDpSt2hKqEh0eAaLgYZCNapj1SPcHSb2YtLW/xVAkAOcHPx7YuuNcunClvrq4XYDFIiUoUDb6Nf9gCSR8wnR2rcDAKW9LZdWFvHtaEb3I46P76pEUuaSNgPZX65mNH72RBkq+IrI/lmfS3Mmni+RZFeSH90xifrUDXPH87Y3Dyk98trKEzvThoGT6firB9qlwOrSre2jAwPzgnNVi3YyJxv3ljJvnT9GXr1NtqKO0Mk8gB5V6GbVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7012","langCode":"en","question":"ipWLWJ+6Hp5tkb+i53yGPBI4Rk2LF/n43i30Vi7AEUt3IPCTcjluvGjJ/WJfejjK","answers":["by","since","for","at"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"kvZ6EzT+hsWWI7SENrTgBqPmVZmxhQhMwU4aitGGBYm/+wYyrBhOcrFR85o1d2NKBHc4Eq2VHohr3pSLv5UP6ni1h4WuS3u5kNkmZiuw/4D03xXEoisM25S8o3JWvoJQh4lH5yrM4P6LflTFoBFRE2I9IJ9FhqHjSgRWDdbGdmOL9dI6Q1p0iHRbcQBcXs6u+pO4LSm2odWWH2vxEjaDaYLOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfKnshJp112AyK4t7QeBzCcrr6eWRDKep0V0oN1kY3BA6Kg6iDiaWcedxPFHhLwnobHmV+Vxro5sDxTx7CgDY+cNCgrWBw2kgNWPRiWXpRPNkzOmr5QoqCVW2B1J3NOqYxP94rUGtpgu14Wl4G4i/GC27FhagzFCzVC5BSAFrKQVtAZTxUY5hyjZpNPAnhyM2ZiMgXx6rNg2iKjnRJyhBlZ2QUEQTmLURav8wJUefJWj1bhzHWvz7gUCR/0uAQhId8r03xXEoisM25S8o3JWvoJQu89EVtYsMT6Bup/jas+4TeaRV04Dhy3Ry2NWymVgxRowUvMz5SFADqBu6omyZpZMcUiKUbUe1MqYuPT+lkyjy3kjenMgKP0jPKu3BBgFH3JuzY31wcjCn02sDtJv2ixrpGj+CziENnNauccrtemtyJqeetzwD9nZB5eLYvFfNjSQ1L6MIy1Kwx1qus31bP2mQZR8Jr5LzONhNpy9tom4nzlw/Hux0pY4QCBz9Y6QlJweiCV6yjWmXi1oENPKhQE7"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7013","langCode":"en","question":"CBtgwmjeHiDPLySiScuPeGdrpMwcOxm26Z9n/Px77HHPfnEuLY0xrEFWiErmC6ET3Ypm4c+2WaI9M3kMfrKDOw\u003d\u003d","answers":["about","with","of","in"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"m9WtPvps0luXdmhlom5DpPw/OeVwcxI2iorSDVF1O9XVjiA/o5s7lnAtKhQsn4ktOxdq4YPQltstoIhs3AZy0wXt20aIyj1LkBSK6pG1PvEQgPgeMRubNnV7R+qdteUtSlsEIL0X73620+bdTA3y0ILOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfJY9esCPEDk2T2nQ4w7dtuhLeLtBPj2Fp3eEbQq2nU0NEdLc8Wl2NeFLmBmqLbpCLG5QfP8Zma9L+hhkKz/iKp6ln65f+GyNbzLo/eKtOzyvAxt0F3Rldg67CsUHDIidPqxE5sDNNzV5gKont9lI7quzgDq1gIQH/uSf5UacY0m95uPR92UThNGMuKmSIVkG9dIY9KheEn1P9oynqpGCITAByV1giKKtZqyTKLYCWALlyfY/i5QD8LG5FteZou0h5qqMOqC34mg7ezpd9+8SWOuQMhg+AqtmZ5p1k2UCCaq8/h9hePovqQRtXlS0tuPg81idZUmV4r1jCP12lV4HQe+1OgC3Rq9oDHtHwOXLtBykZ5fawo61A0Iq2fg8h39jrbQMwsE7gmGLvWH1dHRyJE+4cHTqj0Ntpfyq80ptMFO4jTnRAr6PzbIjf1D64LLj+cy/jLeMu5OxuIATYsdnajlvHCxohlye/9oyXvqQrA8/Hv9Hov+thAGD/dr8fzEKI3+O9+2AGgo1ytQO8VUFdmFggJR49GY9btdGh8FAgPoDxWepzO0GHdrM1unn1m5Qacr7I679fH/XFgbwYky42aqe8lViJ/NC//G5HkdNDbzaWFCycq+qXLHaSBS8EpECivuNhhigfrOdD4q/1DFoSz2AYCXfqSu5Nms6uZ68s0qjsrJRkqMMpo+1+HHu8rrYADMWbySfHYbY+P5+clyv14dQZR8Jr5LzONhNpy9tom4nw1TWHFmZVM4kKnkB4oHnwjamEFhq0A5S8PVu2CMjEBn"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7014","langCode":"en","question":"dweJOHu1WEF+XI6SYyz7rYhuKhTa0+IVurGNLxWqmW/OpxlhklmlI8BG1/vwFrPDk+Wb4oIZfk8q7QxsexHEQ00k4zNzZtejpZPw79nrbtQ\u003d","answers":["to","for","with","about"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"dyZUuldXXaRGYu8WyYGQOUY18Mff/Zls9OnvB7wjEQTAWcHklib01pCzaK183SGJzXzPKY0N+kx0u5efTpWWLI9ECELGO8F5AButheH+qTM347tfLy+D6Oaf3LMWD0wzzAHMra2P1xu/yisJ91OFAnf9Dev2dWQE9+9e+sINLA6PW6Sbga/JM25fsEIYGEm5DLgQ2M1pxXqFaf0PoHckXvSEVdrZhn9VQe9m3o0zOMiGo98ylC80bZ6CWdoGHuZv3NvrYqJB90kB9eTZ0N5puD2Z8/yLKtwjE0xRlhoKhO4t4u0E+PYWnd4RtCradTQ0R0tzxaXY14UuYGaotukIsblB8/xmZr0v6GGQrP+IqnqWfrl/4bI1vMuj94q07PK8DG3QXdGV2DrsKxQcMiJ0+rETmwM03NXmAqie32Ujuq7OAOrWAhAf+5J/lRpxjSb3CU9jKGEzjTNfaPVeKB2DNH5+DEAQtjWGqb4ycQ2i43Zyu3Cgscwl+LKurMfEIvnYQHPjNJ73gXDdxi/2Fk4hPRxpyH7stVM9+dVk6DKERLQBbJq9H3MVXSWagts/GzGZbvEZdJ5E4nBxVFBV+Ncqt+7eNSya2/DVqwoT9Ini3kPqlRY1QKE+WMjXBRBZWyNIQK2Kn/DKR4RgTGQitMbO19e8HwYb8HdVwtvc6n+eH7g04MYjHbPMPZTRGR8zfdWahtmrDmhy1OPiURnu0RYGOXiF3JRYK0O7UC4Ct6hENOcnP213BU3bEs31RUFbpTKJ8UrsqFCLEKYlyHDAwfhW8Ilgn4/yiFF/uzqaRg2Gem+5fdH69hW0gu8/BoaOKxggHC3v2GCrRh3xILs6+mmSAgioe4oytH8/dRSYaQWzasIXRvb/C+7VFGledfLb4Zw0IyjhvewDxEaKFPDJeTZJrKAq6HwFJ55AgnVHuumr6lA\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7015","langCode":"en","question":"0wNS73rqqsQ8HZM1NBMEeQXg3ph7R71n80WFWz7iCXcxXTKiDs6aB3t5vdPfixwk5VBBDb3SbPYwPIMxcx1oDgR2KFA8flsRikG5E7gLxJk\u003d","answers":["of","to","with","at"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"BiEblYZ43PqrG82wdHo1wkuCgldccYVprJxQd9ESqY+ZsJwp2EXr3HZAIFJNSsDPHJ6/5YsWICz1W4Qm6tw0r6+CrMFZc7/5axYT0zCL+AW0iSstnEF/HvUXKwNfroVCLPWwWH60iRccyzH0s09QQ62xknSddLlYGn7UDIGLZMHm50QfO0p0TTKGyajjkvEBGi86UACG2TfLRi4YXN2GA4TfIp56V1a8h6lh/YW+jfOQ3wcupxC0nTaCiDonPMsS8jDMZbdzZp6Q2jgRZNPcyhCnLWs1+j3TBFC7pdLwD9s18i5X6q6HLX8jX4I9Z3VLLAT2dVj/T+WkZXJOCNt9hHjuzZT//MhKlC+ChZGmiQqqoJweCd7thWjKoVIkbS2YpShpf+cDy+lpDjxz6mo2tGSRUVpvIs8EGn6a1ivaduQMFqTrs99rbxFnk7fivRXMInNutSoYQ3svB+Y2yNe3k8StNMogTCJLAwyhpg8SVWgeLNJgPb8dBEcYH9mla7lMr+VM/7SceQl7Uf65nslGMhBCKpibQ2kmgCjb6GxaqAgLtBiaCGVg5D7dkLHCYpB6rvbp0Z+ssigbNWV2qA11ANtAejUD2to9KC8AVg0RyLJDuUVO962LEf05uW2eJhyHGw9k2q6T3PWqCbf36Ognx7qqtwR+bjtNv+N/mmYtCRLr9+aZVFaQHv5IEEjIas829B+qdtlVluzBYJz+WGfqUyy3dJgCchfaBm9lMYYmqgsCwxwiC8OHg3THTac9pGngO7LKTcSqMerCkvou0fQ4P2kmry0e0vn5jfQSg+lLdpUEJckaZKD8qeiHYuV52gTZjirlPBjW/dhZCii/Watf4CRwMJHHxWwvx+C4jH23CpDIYQdnDnh0QEwKu/7BUWn3txc6s7HfOGKb2nFi5omR9RGyykVOQxBhiWAYQu5g6IKAT+K4eDp1notste40WmPnJN/x89lqwECCemPDuApzxf10W0JOEFqW4WwdmTV2evZdm5lLbFyKbQQtT/hLjFe1ymKMdZjI3Us3ObJXub9kkKE8da1zr3p9Ukry2D9qorAiti9rQv05lGHWeaYDc6GS"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7016","langCode":"en","question":"4dNW2sh781vL1lHBJcaitB0qRzONP50JCEI+bBpLlHNdy1zh80aBB7Nd3Mj5Hq2q3+i1JHo4Yd4hbsFPGy/4UQD1KPlfuSPbDyqFr8uhgEc\u003d","answers":["with","about","at","among"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"BiEblYZ43PqrG82wdHo1wkuCgldccYVprJxQd9ESqY+ZsJwp2EXr3HZAIFJNSsDPHJ6/5YsWICz1W4Qm6tw0r6+CrMFZc7/5axYT0zCL+AW0iSstnEF/HvUXKwNfroVCT5BXzfnWYCn/m9sIAonxHcEh3086gOqBQjcAcLXILsdvzVcVOoVJG4QZ1/DVTnFRCvxPfXsw6PRXyITtQRRtqmARPvXdL+i5fJbzCiE+J3TKc13H+nTDFl5k4UK1deEPM2haoI3kzjp2a88Y3jGjZejZdEI6MLWKkGoGptsGRF5KugmUHMI7fsDfIgKzZ2anEDvGmK+UcZhd9z8De52uvGRb0AwGuTkJ15T8M1gnhoD03xXEoisM25S8o3JWvoJQssEpzxnUhuCQyogcYDCMZzLHHnsAit5EFbvGmXlTyqkOQVEDO4TQnFEDJthUvdx5X1ue9Q1tmnENCu0oUi+5sxjjK1yx7RDpoDIQ8fTi2Ki9bZIiYZQtO1LgJalwPYgmzzji6A9wHXJvgmS0nbjFZxjjK1yx7RDpoDIQ8fTi2KgSRBDSXLPqZrx1frfM5gZX1PFGsBOdArqkkNoSRARU07e1m/so5NBCQu1PBQyqp7LAi/T87Mt4sX6VI5TXLOnfhjFgXACrbtX3E0flr8EAPEICx1jVWc9SPmzrAjAMd6raZYd3ofVY5nqB1NfRUVPIW28rjwehdLnJ31VqitfIlS9cw4wGadXyWMaGhO5xbfi5YWxNkh8FrratDH5NFgIcXlvRoTbS98fAUqgORUy4qdqYQWGrQDlLw9W7YIyMQGc\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7017","langCode":"en","question":"S12hf0PmaEjGAmhO87/uk+mnps9Fd3ZM1LSZixmCzOGrRKnVnxswpkbsx1InYMbLkD3Gfo42DjPNLSRJ+VELqGjHBaDySyyN2YiKlZAREDrv08fwm+pLlI31zWBtrbxq4FI+fRQsGodQ86v1bvJnqoRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["with","about","by","for"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"O8ppYWgXDWP75ISyBmd9oAZoh6Knv4Nh1215SGKLoJawm6EFw/Uw2i68WevEoF7YLgb+opSrfcaMh4CGGR1hgzTjIsCUQ1HNAC05cXBguclpB7HPnrHnwveN7SFJQBIoqLkp9PCRRBFE/0rAtseh6SBhPdwKQ3rtyOkNI5EG0ZBidHG4hTwo/wCgF2NEJkZYOHKeiyzbqEJQZLgZWeLRHnOI9tQLdoFhyqohyTWOzz/7LtXG9NBMLGULB2BGaDEH4pBO3lamnvSu2fzbHAX2NlgRN7xFF/kruAZhAkjSSMhiYaAxhnIHaUfwlv2iOGVOw0K07mXitK5KsMvXXDeFIK+yD+UdxyOxyKQ/OLz8lYzXh6cJDiczx+G/NA9uR2VOGrbdNiItquhEJMnERIg5ISYkew6awZr+qzn4nhQWT8+2E19sxfMZbTAxQHZYgOxpsGhyegUK2hDADqgsPJ+0pMaAjubYMCgiUfPNEpsbaYFiIpXjEUM2FoeP+9hJk58uABgR+tvW+GZbcVmmQ3PJjmwt3wijvYPEVm5NrX/ScXMDR49uitpoZ0wBHqn3BPvgrEUDVK0NLbnHw0NOdKOqI2j177H8wTgQq84UUSYrReOFGCFV0LysnGXqmeqUnvIPaQfM8Vs6Rh9LdOJAXW+CBdsvK8IVWHodijPWPcEcfmRA2qz82htPx96yd2oPaLhggFaqphTeH9a6i4nL82vx/cjimdDM2mnrpnFSnLwzho0\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7018","langCode":"en","question":"z4H8ePsgrndXspudvtv9rRxNKxrYFCZF0BTmMdqVNzHAUeIgHN+II4lkpQ4inW+eDLfWlgnD+YtuidIYW9AzmQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["inside","toward","of","about"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"dyZUuldXXaRGYu8WyYGQOUY18Mff/Zls9OnvB7wjEQTAWcHklib01pCzaK183SGJm9WtPvps0luXdmhlom5DpPw/OeVwcxI2iorSDVF1O9XVjiA/o5s7lnAtKhQsn4ktOxdq4YPQltstoIhs3AZy0wXt20aIyj1LkBSK6pG1PvEQgPgeMRubNnV7R+qdteUtSlsEIL0X73620+bdTA3y0ILOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfIyenzkaDGINB8dgLEaqPfspwkWJtwXUctYjX4sk3IRfmQKQU2jtQhO+C7zAQEBleTK3y8ixdWph8fmFtOwCq4uOVZqfl5mSA4Fb5mHheG7RbeT7IMGYeWSTM5b9KhDNQAH1TjJnkE+7Ur019dPqmK1OYUIWy0iRAST60o3VIRbBZ3auYnn7KFAHvycDhLyDullq7QaiIvc5YoWSyn+8e+K9Amek0K2Q02hW7A+AbJUjUTa7cWQY2jcRDRg6zftuCGI4wLnGwYX19LkAM08um+n4daIxNOhy/XvzeAczq8vTzANrjGMEFtPXZMEMp3QbTEoysyX1pN0nzBPJBdZZ0ehDqkyTtoTwYj7R6P1kLFC5gWOCvMJMco5DhdNUYiB8xI\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7019","langCode":"en","question":"iiEhKe3eh26/QYxenlmVScBhBPo5jrcBxl4MTDiaeByZU4BXHx4+ja9qEtuSAY5pujdHyKqflFcv/ovHhimXyUwOuE3CawVCkMNSJg9hDmm3BymO91TzEfI//uxANDqb","answers":["for","into","along","outside"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"O8ppYWgXDWP75ISyBmd9oAZoh6Knv4Nh1215SGKLoJawm6EFw/Uw2i68WevEoF7YLgb+opSrfcaMh4CGGR1hgzTjIsCUQ1HNAC05cXBguclpB7HPnrHnwveN7SFJQBIoqLkp9PCRRBFE/0rAtseh6SBhPdwKQ3rtyOkNI5EG0ZBidHG4hTwo/wCgF2NEJkZYOHKeiyzbqEJQZLgZWeLRHj+YVmlvJ/5g2El1+cdoQic0N1MtI2A3bF7ioivParVsUKPB7sOISXr+NX2OSGallluVaGxylZUO8Ht7hFPz1PwU2n7SIU0f6uXfXnikXAwV2lKQFxZ5MhIuorxs0tLZvAaHETvMGHDRm3MUXRDr1y+1V1AitmKK3g/uzbmKxJAD2Fv0NdiEpS1o0MA9jZ1xniouJaYavVc56NuqnQG9KMzuU698aNTZFbFx+lD3zWuki6GwAn7Ar/H0vRDKI2LzKB82VbXYlAn5nuO/p7wjRVMYGCz50vrQ5gdk5KUO+WR7EK7vVIRyMwNbo5E6WGV8p5nm8MlNwFCao0fhY4EYIIzQFuVkd5wqd847DvjkfyJeHPBWiltiOCKJG5Sx36wTfpzOanR1A11Toq0OseFMOFR95Ibpz0Byof8kIUsyDgpqP8f73xwhqtg1wq7EC8/uclVAgvX/ttU7MkkOXB2zh+2YO1KpfXE/04kPaIiCe7CTDh0aTt5FMYXpHo84ChQbCuEQ8GXNAIjqs7AihIsWnVezKL8DVDXuEnJa5SHlkt9vmJ6bpjd2GK3aP3CvJrQGHHSHHyn1lMluUahfq/rWy5r+CWpNYtS0mlh/NdZcHG2oT9uzUY1kQ4nu9yl4+PPpjD85FOIlTwY8fJaSkNQ8MXppdAtMRwSrMETC+UST2+GlMwbs8+HKFaRxfjIwJ0J3Zw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7020","langCode":"en","question":"N+xXt17Gg6Q6l223tAaxi95WdTYYzGrvJxiClSXuFGzVY8gL3kZ6u+m6oPmzLRlqzFOzZBVhSFWfBq7h1ptnmQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["among","to","during","between"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"X62FBBzQR30/ot4yI4eOpVeuaAtZOw52IJeI5tvUIAoqtU3FNlmRffYi7hQ7Ky8gepo8xiIPbAv3FDem6ERxelL9Lk/WzP4zzoXMWcOiFliEJPrL3o55DnxrwCc0nrRRUK12v560waoUKivveiyB7yn4jTaVyXEUg3Nn2JISJynARapWw6SIq/L4PVb0JrmcGOMrXLHtEOmgMhDx9OLYqL1tkiJhlC07UuAlqXA9iCay5bqYXPgYA6EMYEbp6+a/QCSN4fNhaHhXUj3P2FI+FNcjzz/fT/MUO6XjUcmpGiYIAcdcxSRlKsM6CoNZ0RkfgDWWEM2M/qhAAz0UIFg3n7mZITtuLpas/lJ8PDyLnWQeoMckr8u7JcbuB3zuImByYZdfT4mlObacoMCrN7v00u8TBzrIz2rvpAy9bp3+0lno7eISpZWiMs07hCDFpkRyRi9S4t9DMC2pViFlvWQDjS4dIhvGk6KuEzLEkqMNAvdtU7soQYK380569/6lMggWUa2pzkQasLsPu6BerPcjykejqz8ivywYS+q7iCSitnVWqMrWaOfy8WK7NTtYiUx2B/7lVnfVC4laemyP70YnE+Bro/FEbRx5TVxpZ9JgQZJnBPTManRuzzADrgO4nHWx0nz73R3PwOhMjnqZbEE67kDarPzaG0/H3rJ3ag9ouGCAVqqmFN4f1rqLicvza/H9Z8tBH1rD+eSzhP0ekPmMhw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7021","langCode":"en","question":"N6kK2E4GZ98iCd4/tcVYlQGxT+vgb2XrSeWeiPEfUUab0wTFYiCDgsP/MRI6uFHpQadggtoaE5uMCFDXkAQqpA\u003d\u003d","answers":["toward","across","among","between"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"d7V1Q0zPI6M63udL66D1i/kjmboWgrOSrT6enKp31pXgffFuqbLKQPz5eF7g/sseHAR4bS5OLtn5KY4oFTdf3OgOjiEppGTBAAS099GrSqb0O1chVDWzJ2gpNGB33rBzgeJsGwOcGz0kMZlwS1ijfDKdlcU3mANoe0jeQsV/QokpyqE3pLWQ6zafl9XkitPPt/1MvKCYA7PSGlE/Dr97DgC3xbvShahUImG17s7LN9KB96rRozwg39NHkdARpDpU4G9cClKjkqoCWNp76sD7ksnhdZKTuAfi+CKQiv2QAfYUqy/kb97WF30NnS6rCYh2XOH3tHIl5KzcwbMSDEKUDr5c8qgS49+GMBiyIWHCdykFLUCuuRQ3r9ewBlWOiRCekAPGm6kjAGRA5QutgEo8wyqxeiGngZZ4EpH+psvgig0l4szBTrHvl/5M8oUD5CPId61j5gU6RhpSEcEBaGmwy7O/aGRUyELVjrL1ETM5xRJ/WFtUOR/XvAngDADNrVkYGfnFwpC6r0e42PYt5G+ZTsrHU6Chj1MeZ0wb6B1Cmo6L1jmLJ2IyN6x05BuWRvNQc+NSwVojbRgFSbo3NooQvsB2VSZSwvlKKXE+MY1kxBNpdAtMRwSrMETC+UST2+GlHxp3fj6U7z8PSyYK7QIG1YRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7022","langCode":"en","question":"/E1rVFAj7TO7W/hLBr5RgKpFKKzgmJ4b4+hdjNGY7sF8Sd2vxOYiUqvLENMxhZ7ojXI7bMbmqZnEoHljkDkL15IsGw7j4o6uWldZDMG5Qy0\u003d","answers":["toward","during","between","to"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"jFSH1ZgZO1exRtINd4fQS3818b/x0UPVBmfQVR5vAEoMqPS5n2UBbcJmAc5OSB7Tw0wBoEJcYSKOoGM4xCi6D+cExo0IbhmvFKYFF413pw+1yFaVk8zCzUZtuWMeYFYAAItkVyofhPr7h84SWhuaswPxl6LwVJHjKRtBo3xOSDsrbnEZi/H9ywcaK+VH/GkxmCCSw5w8o1/u0l7zVdnJb1UP8fiIugWUYiW6Po10ZeTPyl8nxgtY02H1aSE4SwotQQMR2G0uSP2z6rtASZxt+gaxhGSJLE6DmSr2WIoV6CmMIPpbO0kdOu+DqSx+msKp2PCZDbneauW5Q0Ewm+u0EK6QpO8fHpHMGfx9v50LbEsfnpYapeKxwa3RYBU5TXv/LyrQ4u7ICS98ATdxq2COvifimeUbkRYL9Qy2MtFUZA2qoJweCd7thWjKoVIkbS2YpShpf+cDy+lpDjxz6mo2tGSRUVpvIs8EGn6a1ivaduQMFqTrs99rbxFnk7fivRXMInNutSoYQ3svB+Y2yNe3k8StNMogTCJLAwyhpg8SVWgeLNJgPb8dBEcYH9mla7lMr+VM/7SceQl7Uf65nslGMhBCKpibQ2kmgCjb6GxaqAhZZGW+HwjA62+bSOGOzQQW5s0oxBUVRca9xrMXOqbciulvbIxrdiOSxtte6n1rux8vRwlP2H7BU64gdUOcw2iz"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7023","langCode":"en","question":"kSuo6Ax5lTymEb1qrvsYm4LC7RAwZbkEBX2A3ErbnKHhELL8mRPru9mnQSgaZkLvfayg5CjYj7A7eWy8gQo4HcIMv08irNq9+xohKbqemaQ\u003d","answers":["near","behind","opposite","between"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"jFSH1ZgZO1exRtINd4fQS3818b/x0UPVBmfQVR5vAEoMqPS5n2UBbcJmAc5OSB7Tw0wBoEJcYSKOoGM4xCi6D/DNM+rvV3yIP7FcT5Ae0hxwPKf/meOCLnuBfg3PUKF/nwIt/QhwvW4zAXxZceVq5EenMDYibFvQY43qaNjAKJKaSlDb0qlsufHhiaSRZKjW9tstoBB/raf/FUEIoLLI8P8ffMyHJxo49YqVp+a3KhFBYGf8Xkgs6EbSDWeLQ/ygO6NgmGCdYJuePvc8IRxy4iHmK+C6ss6MjOPZGoK3E4Xj7KmOZzzM/3MbhWJFOAaOJSkNA0HxWtke5QeN2qLaiULld2P8tcpewvSZs4tdko0gxP2HHxLaJ9hSwcKbyBQ9PptQBZ3hu0fA8JGFLwAxRWmioF8ma3bJ+Z1WG2VotAnhft7ZyQuPrp0oS+826Shae307RPL8ZmLHRQtx1SX7Rg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7024","langCode":"en","question":"7RrLNo6D4SDlwm7eLrkmUtatlJwPIV6j4ljrb6PHMEPFm1YXPwDG3lQJmvR3D6nTp6rsPFLwD6I69YOiNrrRMQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["to","until","opposite","for"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"PL+YAMRM9D6J2+vS/6xDMZXzD713jePcYxA1ujSjRgqGWGGyCE8zBlMJxeMKCvpn6F5hN//iSlYPlDwHYw0+d/bDP1S6QDpFMslpXyTnv4LqSumceK89TLBFkb999P/udIiQfk1AqOMKvqYvNfaHG/rwaIJ9z5wdFCRbq9HB2gtnghGkY6bAfVz3aVWfHPQdJGFb4xoGA2JXBJkJrc6fMSHQYrhzOwSa6mScuz/zlJk+CaymqU59BHwYM4goWCCsDEsCo1cxugcicJLiB9afPxF2fRyACwd07GUAEjtUUPvZYBncmLxxoGElHz4IhfuUsHtiTyrzPUB8CuWZ/69pDKDOXzcQViWUjn/y7kaixoOdwZRAKXsRB+1vmMIYM2fXq2umTYKqanEtrZkwB2U8hTMCnZ0Ao/ARwbpnZb02sIKJRm6UtCdPgzj4cFxYXdgRuQpbCDROSMVKkhtjxjjPUfROgWoZoeztP/xlqpzHa/Wx/bY/qFx+PGjPbqi2pxbADBMMNkpBhyo2Fw0cTwmiSF44wgEgKmvO/uNHRdSPEKS0e/dYSOZqKrp/xNkuBtpW6MwHjWZ6AvXLHJdlUDJrhTQ6KI9RZ2854NgXULbD/frmzSjEFRVFxr3Gsxc6ptyKCc/TDMZCPYp+sJ3VZAm0YMIjEwq8I/7mnzpCJC0u1SQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7025","langCode":"en","question":"kBlbpBFpnT4eU+3q45vl7+T6BI12qSkiKbFXMECdzc66p1s1q3sjp1eSVoUWEKyM57///r8lLLYrEsPuqrY73A\u003d\u003d","answers":["behind","before","between","for"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"0CNqOxVahBHrCFfhLDJKf5b23sIx6kG61/4YylPBc6TQJOb8dU205O2AZbV7bKgefcxWbkHfbRP+iPE/PWNQU0hbb0V9Cb1hP4X29tRH7U+WiD9qTMACOLkco/+zze+2jFSH1ZgZO1exRtINd4fQS3818b/x0UPVBmfQVR5vAEoMqPS5n2UBbcJmAc5OSB7Tw0wBoEJcYSKOoGM4xCi6DzV6qOlGW1ZkVj+oO1IY29W3eWn6oGRCGeH6dyS42iYfbiTJvQ1M2jWaD98ta/9jqGbrEBCGpHBTtzZ6mI1+vTzjDQnuI4sQSAE5H20z9HPqeK1leOCNY6Y/IUfhdddJZCU8vdukLDmYGw+CoQNP1uWH/n/w8j0EPAwu+rD7Gv+J6Vr7/TYlqXh6sOW+i5CicH9rolgRxpmDWvpd/ci0iRRHkKIXhlD3UwKu6QBVRP1yKOGE4h0vFfYxuZCQud84lrTp6wxgfJeUWgEDHkZ7hx3NqDz5pTQ0b9ngsg01y439"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7026","langCode":"en","question":"oDmVHhBwXYHGwYbRkGbMalP+s3CFshSuE+7Tw7iWHb6zE97HguAlSctfrWnmu9/3G2ahmAnS4n3KK5KAHJZR2xTWtOyackLzpuB146Zg5HcJN/fAmGZouOt3L/PFSg58g7gQTuFE9q4r2VJNjBZc3w\u003d\u003d","answers":["with","about","to","in"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"BiEblYZ43PqrG82wdHo1wkuCgldccYVprJxQd9ESqY+ZsJwp2EXr3HZAIFJNSsDPHJ6/5YsWICz1W4Qm6tw0r6+CrMFZc7/5axYT0zCL+AW0iSstnEF/HvUXKwNfroVCP1KyLap7o9N6fjFNEIAt7kwpcN2E0bgjNvql4R1c9OAx/FQ0jMKcU/tf0vh8FDzWs+1MHGV/cHupTLuQL+AJl30Mutn3Z2ELUj7eimqeSqpvYAV3MQDFpl/UR5ccJnqPh12USgfqWqfI6ZzkFJ69xCJP4cq+LHFkIy0bPdVs93dMcUngJfiZ8P/FmfrBw4qGvXqCtt2qAosdd5KrjYIXTC6/MiP8CT+HVPPadD2t7idyUtic7QE4/3h0CnjmXvJgZthZMWBrWz+0FszQkgOSeDJiGcoGbYB0+bLBZS4kHBAEDiYy8jKmkb3G+ZVCDp+RyRGcag0e2XtQt2/dySNPA1jdZu2QPaQX6ooPNwetwW+mTf7Y+iCaldI0Nwx0oDxaFJv3UFA7p8LcF2BsidmZDdKHRxZtZ0dxviwVhBpfvAkynqA4qa0+k5rrLzPDG3PGjdxhp8Awnrf2aFvbrt+c2VnemjTdrnzdaxY3BvUQK9Rlp0TOMnGUmZWN/t8LK1L4zC5yoK0P/iFyKSMm9X2PUOS3JX63eRjwwVbbLe0KSp+js3NtnbZzW6BH9WyWQUk0MDDoJs2R3TPvxQwNB/Ik2HzAzKvTBOXdiX6jiTdAcwx223hssYnDldix7vdt5T56xPwdz8WSsDzSAcq5ETP2afh1o/Q+XfpcHyfaV/tGVC9M9aiX8A8S5U6y4G1FUBQzFRqacRiy4SuuuZGFbqmdTEKP1ZHs43meayDpv0iTvWGdaEFA4M1KmtaWuoxAZqSZN7g9+hYS/Tz4x0HMtstvMhbfpDb+nW6NM2my64EOao6UCM3CXWHID7iMlJPRCVK+5s0oxBUVRca9xrMXOqbcikzcco1iaD211iN5qYr4i0aiA0HzpUMxJQa8nDbEfjqg"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7027","langCode":"en","question":"ZeiYGhCt8W68FFfA8x/JTDQ6JzG6adZMPU3EbdRjRRSu5VxyufV/c7OFa4Gky0MEVnYeNAmu3tiNrTL98O3EIw\u003d\u003d","answers":["of","about","on","in"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"dyZUuldXXaRGYu8WyYGQOUY18Mff/Zls9OnvB7wjEQTAWcHklib01pCzaK183SGJm9WtPvps0luXdmhlom5DpPw/OeVwcxI2iorSDVF1O9XVjiA/o5s7lnAtKhQsn4ktOxdq4YPQltstoIhs3AZy0wXt20aIyj1LkBSK6pG1PvEQgPgeMRubNnV7R+qdteUtSlsEIL0X73620+bdTA3y0ILOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfL+9QcB8gjnQY0DyiWeDh+V6tT8bKxVvC9LXcj46BwAkNyP4ffkxqPWCRCsgEIRcuL3lmPFTwi2ruo5L24NqQJyJ/m1nW4Zhz8MvoefJEROzVmx/cXmA2qfiZs9uj4CX+x6T15ky/tEISLO94RbSaW74Ct+YRjMf2M+eZqfWVFN4AtTlHkIAAdHUa9m2nbrsTR45znMXjYZ5APB53lHOXUWPaBm2+APQUjOL9xxiD1UCAt1mbMnQx4dUNCwm+XK9n3W1lW3rGp0KMmS6VUCsJV60jy6kzx+UVvhSckQ4mx3THemDRhLZI9ZdruuADpYkhmuQyopRAJFlaGOpdVM/KAexA85bbu25oTty0NjZ9SGUL46tFplsLDG00lfiihqJF2PrOPl3pr3WqGpUs9bS2bsp++OVG/6houxgovDrliNqwnekROtEy607UOTw5lPvARmuxQguo3ZpFyRBzpaAnSllKCLvAbhtBcFFUUp9HgVq0h+y30iwUc5TLgtLiMYPryjuHXhrRjoUbq4/l/617LotnLf9ksTMKGtUEK6g5zv/uf4RHgwniTpNn7gmkmeczO+aJPDfBa4ocBwg/qFb9OSYzNWK4nXlmOECZZzO4IgnaetFrlvg8L6SggphmFqw7aIQUS46PuFKm3ckqFo6a1g1MYTVQkOB8dVDZ4WSatApeCZuB3rXFDbOoKGYl6QmRUmlSphFkqW8zMrf+1Mp9PGgGypXP51W9lJnFvbdgyn2y96/qQ0R/xJIfLf9yGwVSNhXvtqP5brgq9FDfU/5J8AZhjJMUuwvzIfqWwMGMHWoLLysB8Rjxxa3sUk/4jP28qrCbqbhs1/6pOB6Ff/5TKGLbY8x/ZChD1wBqqlI5mtSdMcL/P180Stu8zjFjINpyDwaD9vNeoVh3eDMszhjDECvFO7z5+xRz34QACByPZ4iubNKMQVFUXGvcazFzqm3IrsbqHnVOZP5sgd29hgomfNk+4zhFZ44ti+DYzhv7sr8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7028","langCode":"en","question":"+VN2DGd9aMaHGr7dbX9RmQV6uzzPyKvzCUr0UCjcR1girreiiw1KV01w4UuEZZLjAbq6xiAe0y0AZOC/9SSeqQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["between","of","towards ","at"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"m9WtPvps0luXdmhlom5DpPw/OeVwcxI2iorSDVF1O9XVjiA/o5s7lnAtKhQsn4ktOxdq4YPQltstoIhs3AZy0wXt20aIyj1LkBSK6pG1PvEQgPgeMRubNnV7R+qdteUtSlsEIL0X73620+bdTA3y0ILOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfI1vogr46O8S9JKQcKPBQsjnlEjhwvTjFdkcmCSbPokSgBhRcdcWHGG5zaec+1myTWat4AYudpDMEAnlOW5sPnjrvbp0Z+ssigbNWV2qA11AIB2vKLcMskaiwcDB9qeiZthyWSnA3JEV3/HPf2d+QBapwkWJtwXUctYjX4sk3IRfg0TgxzcREsAKCqGCOuywxbv9XJrdBGNCqBEFgxDQM1q+UWohgv114ufq1B29cChBxX5zberVFo+Q3RlLEX+fniZ5OzLnWRR55FDhUoVsV+DLsH2vn4rGEcJ+NBUphpMaA6mCjj1Mbjib25yd4slqd1oWVhTEI3Y1pfvrzmviI1irxIMbmVhw08F+hhdRtG4UILIsbI4ni8Tuhb+aRBQFjYKnXjbIHR/Jba+dqog1ioKF0IKmz3RsYdVlP5uhNJzPkTPEQEQS8p7VqIo5CA/qg2PAmgN8/E41cpeNjm/W4LfCYYtSOt/39yEbZh5OklDdZ5QzHckfqhmx9gx3F+Cx0uNbU8qo9aUIyJe2v8EEm2sC2WKDiJEjCYgTKzj7A0YHJsSSPMf2VCxC/4eoA7FqkhcKfzLkKaK1SSWfom8KmkF65P+YktyV0CSSj8oVzNy11uDsbOpqgw1SkljGKExVP8OWCeNKEBNK9AmPGe90kc+BIT/1GOdjhpuxdd9jVYiYH7wUqbMsT4z7BEZU2OF8jh7fTtE8vxmYsdFC3HVJftG"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7029","langCode":"en","question":"VZ6cxoLax83eql1Olw3gDaB4fWNiA4nOAxpurdpq0b2Wa70USB2Hmwuj0O76EogMo/2YaftF/bUeN/E5yWfy182JDWjC0F/k9kxDxUv/6MpUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["about","in","beside","after"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"VHKpkhknz8QmFNuw/Z6WeparwLDRinlrOLgXou92yWa0WQKO6dfKOkDHdakd0FJWJHHpUcPGKIIZmYXy42a1nxJJuUSnrsOnOP6ctVB704zYpJ5d3S898Dlv6H46qKTXYoaS5y56FxUs3ludVzOProxT+RThZv1A96IllQoN6oi7GBxIPHaTW7+JYpa/EsMEzY2SUqEQWw4A7Ouf93xaA3lHuDNL1FLjf4IC/GmrEtHqerGoEyT/MpbQZGUuE0NfinDqCRgxLhQDccQnNbLXjTu4EfwVRy9QJEV23QjSAPljGJve8vjOolKjlPFGquolFNq4SkXAVmhcwPacylIFt2w6tUeM3DXSpGZYbbhRjdqN5sIPLcvwOGHTbU73Im/tggKCFxdt77tBbWoenW4cMFe7KsHyk9kQXNv6PkYgcq8TvKdlX3845Nadv4ItWwhWzTHOAteEBwpE79luX3nzrFZS9t+wavSmGoUBzNWCLfAK5YK2ryWcxd29/AkYdpjshyVa3i66RIoaGRQ10PE/83h5j2kqcLemBFF8g+ebAEqR8+8toED14zwM6ISdBOuKO8IFmaV7bqEUbB1dUNxQR/G0hT+GAyNiiEdxK/qzsn7t0RfTc2JzkYhB9BaEQVXovPqJag87+eXVnJAGdMoKKhTIgzDxMyJ25Cxv3YiF+mlcM+OubUP4rVagFv7NAxTXjf75Gj47jRbvhPha5oeyZfYrPklMs0YLUKbnPhprtHUUfN/js7+N7rpi6IHTKpy9Qf+QzIk7bKpxZyNaOnspVEMgzE1+vky4dJawpy4pZHS5YWxNkh8FrratDH5NFgIc1lmvCgxx9EbKK3BnEEq/BJPuM4RWeOLYvg2M4b+7K/I\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7030","langCode":"en","question":"TS08SClv5bY+x5dk5lm2a5hMXF1AWy3KODu240xFnunJhOE+2sDhkP9gKdC9156wuuZYNoK+5R1fc2bUCoNaAlpljMEYOENuO+uNdvIncXhUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["by","at ","for","near"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"Osvykcw0EfbL0RTsVL6PMfsu1cb00EwsZQsHYEZoMQfikE7eVqae9K7Z/NscBfY2WBE3vEUX+Su4BmECSNJIyGJhoDGGcgdpR/CW/aI4ZU7DQrTuZeK0rkqwy9dcN4Ugc4LfoW7UgftmGqP9Z13B+4ar1D5kjMBYDTDXHkDbna0m0RHPIPQ7EmPOLTBla4lxbOgioFzlzYdLVuR8kOdZHXTcpGYMq3GJAWOMYpalvKSVCmfgsMxfXJtvWQjZkpagfn4MQBC2NYapvjJxDaLjdnK7cKCxzCX4sq6sx8Qi+dhAc+M0nveBcN3GL/YWTiE9HGnIfuy1Uz351WToMoREtAFsmr0fcxVdJZqC2z8bMZlu8Rl0nkTicHFUUFX41yq37t41LJrb8NWrChP0ieLeQ+qVFjVAoT5YyNcFEFlbI0hArYqf8MpHhGBMZCK0xs7XGCAAU+AU83ZU4Kon297B7s3gyeevI4RyBXlsaH56qIQg7azdixJrwfhM+FUWnsMuj4flOxo/3rgG9JaM4BSHwc9yTOKEoF8Jy32mp51Qh3Tx3U8OzXSX2WeqQT9CFCQ+o+ZVmbGFCEzBThqK0YYFifRz2s3JOgpPdjiARA7OTkHsiMhTcttO66cXw1I9XkxKfDBSWNKxCNeW0zg1jgWka/HxDhcNsoQRM/w4qSi7dbbDL39dBBC3mF8hHKoacW5d9GWaB0nYqVY+kn0ZXHodQ+szXgrd72ktCoVf+TIWRlYP+bB17SPZ/qga4LV/svOlXYkCqPZ4+cUp9oTnUmtmDG7+pdkOg1z0Sodei1MLFg7mzSjEFRVFxr3Gsxc6ptyKLCS/lC2IkZkMw3hoE26RZ5PuM4RWeOLYvg2M4b+7K/I\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7031","langCode":"en","question":"Y5OqJP/KYGrIpmtc5BmRRAtqSwIpAJaNZWDkA5FZa6SM6Pcr+3uJLidJISQ8cXLSkywCUNNzCXFNiSar0rkAZtscgJ5r+XPOBGO9Rb5WcaY\u003d","answers":["for","at ","inside ","on "],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"O8ppYWgXDWP75ISyBmd9oAZoh6Knv4Nh1215SGKLoJawm6EFw/Uw2i68WevEoF7YLgb+opSrfcaMh4CGGR1hgzTjIsCUQ1HNAC05cXBguclpB7HPnrHnwveN7SFJQBIoqLkp9PCRRBFE/0rAtseh6SBhPdwKQ3rtyOkNI5EG0ZBidHG4hTwo/wCgF2NEJkZYOHKeiyzbqEJQZLgZWeLRHkUeooFVO2PdGjgVXbKTmfvROTYrGZ/9YsTRoncd51yLvm5XT17iVo/mIIrpMbMl+i+lQJBdEqPwYq8ACvM143KeUSOHC9OMV2RyYJJs+iRKQQrpM6G6uERAR5r91vnTaggFV540IftjDoDDBcJ/qvYa1dTWo9WY5awOLLyGQwKkB9SaApcc0rNxmx74zz1QeaaXTWyDxRrMaR0YAPz+/KUS6Laoe2daeJyapLkjfdGl+HbAHOOhEHcDjIo0Ax9yRfTfFcSiKwzblLyjcla+glAKFFEBaiw0mldi3K+KvuUXG7HCE/Uvew7TjJ+9LuMaiA/67JP+5LsSUUKPJchYuXEG3K55EAVdh8FuICGqIVyVV+BasZyGGb6GYQc0PHHe5iO5736ZO7ldhLqE7NLwC9gxGYOczFOYDRRS473B+r0RYYDrvNbuRJegPnp1LwpYvzbsnrW5yAZ0Hd7+YM7rxPbJs91Sv2t0f2+PnAzbGRllIvRHQ5k60E0/f/A/2p2aXo3mwg8ty/A4YdNtTvcib+0kbPJkjH3Y/5YYeZk9Bsso8mLNbBTZeYdYKSYVaqarOGpLgwQIzSCp1GuikPG/cbCPrOPl3pr3WqGpUs9bS2bsh5+JCT5aV7YbvNHafus/Rdo9cWbfp117uDz8T64F86KUirY+oKGU+/h2nvviNrx99eXJLoGw9hZaCW+dAsJc1e3GJnsLTDQaj6d20EwYLS4KRv5XKCb5sGZOzfsjZZUAQtKWQlL6x4JJLxjfJinHR6uY2mp9cepkLUHS4fy9QgSvPPwsFE6xqr4QFSbTzUeywh3M4U+25Z0v26Ae0y8qOJ/o+1pK7/89GALwIjEyQT6Q6iljLFJMNJ9MGxXAV11BscLud+fscbuRtBgP4raJZ+nzoc7LSohuSz9oMwQxMLUMmSRbhTevxh//MPv1CvmX91xOI1jLJGR9HT3AfHV78kVePL7kNXiymvYaQ7kGe7833lquvnhR7om+crj3tsjRIyjhvewDxEaKFPDJeTZJrJVsnJoP0GHnbZxM4j0VQOY\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7032","langCode":"en","question":"fCLyvb8KPUTxFnyEv1+nsjIER++hiRc72kU7MZNUnrxxSKe7s1UI2zu1len0sY9K8DRKwKOmHohYepleKB6yeA\u003d\u003d","answers":["of","between ","among ","about"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"dyZUuldXXaRGYu8WyYGQOUY18Mff/Zls9OnvB7wjEQTAWcHklib01pCzaK183SGJm9WtPvps0luXdmhlom5DpPw/OeVwcxI2iorSDVF1O9XVjiA/o5s7lnAtKhQsn4ktOxdq4YPQltstoIhs3AZy0wXt20aIyj1LkBSK6pG1PvEQgPgeMRubNnV7R+qdteUtSlsEIL0X73620+bdTA3y0ILOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfIN2xw7fj5DNK/Tovtcl5z4C7f6RI/FKkhiIlIzKddDnmcJDb3c4oioQ9IlyIrliGD/RZqlzFIc/hsQJoK3Kz/0IbIdHWaYDUzKI+TlphuyNP0aJ6wcirErnn1dFllXqHHGGAi2axmFjkd1P9Ul0aTEn28sRzaZo6yTLLQIXOifPNUDio6mxf6NoRNUTpRqE+9kid6vpBS7Bf534dYVIFOvOoEZas3hZldJ7yu8/9Vid2VTkG65gb7Sd0Z05Pc1fdVyP2E/K8F0DKWqaSzSpxRBjqZIXNrhts8wvhdrLZgaaengdBemom7h3YErtqwNyLW+rVA6GPQUqJ/kxuyh6bxJQMkIRArDIArhMfulRwD2CnKR9DaGHz+8Y2+u/+p6GGDJUWWfP1mxpgt9fh4rNeIlBIT/1GOdjhpuxdd9jVYiYH7wUqbMsT4z7BEZU2OF8jgL4Dyk2Ddhmb3VPFKKU98L"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7033","langCode":"en","question":"U5wMmsHHpSjHibKvyT5V2W1MnykH+aEysHyBtP1rfnZSeuQKMlEomzYLxrVSIjTr96Ze7JMHnkFaSul1HfQoBUh1Unj6nd1niCxoBWuj8ITPqwf571W6wuMDYgnbSbxy","answers":["behind ","to ","among ","of"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"zXzPKY0N+kx0u5efTpWWLI9ECELGO8F5AButheH+qTM347tfLy+D6Oaf3LMWD0wzzAHMra2P1xu/yisJ91OFAnf9Dev2dWQE9+9e+sINLA6PW6Sbga/JM25fsEIYGEm5DLgQ2M1pxXqFaf0PoHckXvSEVdrZhn9VQe9m3o0zOMiGo98ylC80bZ6CWdoGHuZv3NvrYqJB90kB9eTZ0N5puCY1JWmRG2hIssD+02R3YYcAJn/UJTOAjGM+LHb7cdDEJHHpUcPGKIIZmYXy42a1nxJJuUSnrsOnOP6ctVB704zYpJ5d3S898Dlv6H46qKTXYoaS5y56FxUs3ludVzOProxT+RThZv1A96IllQoN6oi7GBxIPHaTW7+JYpa/EsMEzY2SUqEQWw4A7Ouf93xaA3lHuDNL1FLjf4IC/GmrEtHqeHVAKoWN4oe/IyjyalWxC7f6RI/FKkhiIlIzKddDnmcJDb3c4oioQ9IlyIrliGD/RZqlzFIc/hsQJoK3Kz/0IbIdHWaYDUzKI+TlphuyNP0aJ6wcirErnn1dFllXqHHGGAi2axmFjkd1P9Ul0aTEn28sRzaZo6yTLLQIXOifPKdFNhlOJqVAa1hoeSJ4IdHOaynwsUSkQ65Fo5iNLM4hrstMl4kMlxpAI5mWBMHJA4kmYGjGEAjtdlqlzzaTmErxlNaRRQ08Hwwjfas8r7rO8MXg0mkTne6rhTAzgrbmOkGUfCa+S8zjYTacvbaJuJ9XMyFZMf+BaDzH5v92e6sE2phBYatAOUvD1btgjIxAZw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7034","langCode":"en","question":"x4IA52t2Uwf+Y0axKhiI8s4lWAM3pIb7TFCO6yR1xtkYWfNR+uQjRmNI/F5hAMW0G/nVcxLFxD5rHFkdjg3uMLamEAPAEd1NPRNfGlQ1cN+QYqGk/R3bBvBUYkB3ic20","answers":["since ","inside ","to","along"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"aKzRRpGTGTTsZMIepq/GeTf6DifAVPHLYbF303AJ3KgxejZ1Flqit8X/c9EV11MlIh1diH5jyf//yCNV9HcVARvwe3S/+A5QQZV1g+NrtSyqoJweCd7thWjKoVIkbS2YpShpf+cDy+lpDjxz6mo2tGSRUVpvIs8EGn6a1ivaduQMFqTrs99rbxFnk7fivRXMInNutSoYQ3svB+Y2yNe3k8StNMogTCJLAwyhpg8SVWgeLNJgPb8dBEcYH9mla7lMr+VM/7SceQl7Uf65nslGMhBCKpibQ2kmgCjb6GxaqAjRT2Wg85eeW5xT86JOtTa6i2CeGT4GgQg5kbX4d0Yr2tAGmmQdKAWKc6qH2MAAc5waDcWnvlviC0hd8Jc2v88JNad9Mh0AAnDKDLjgR6p5jo5WBrZhBqsj+YGwg+zbLPjxkMvQR9qFDXZxYEFs8ES+CadgVC7CIKKcaOB/svjZcRx/TIZdJJvFUKN0Xk6GAHiJBYO+/qdvp1zYlh6U12ayArPkLKxP2ZPAm1uwag/mEPX+i4OMuM3Pyh1NhWoCeBLGKRYhQlNCz4dY4yyBEguTrVxO6/Cw2YVW9ZxGugUchcYMXk394mvNLXu7ur4+UuWZHKb7ySk+VFrgXneRrCuZQZR8Jr5LzONhNpy9tom4n1czIVkx/4FoPMfm/3Z7qwTamEFhq0A5S8PVu2CMjEBn"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7035","langCode":"en","question":"5Zt06w3COs3yjLnOFDjOV/ML3GNVG4YIsXe80O3PffCkah6IG3XZ13Ql0tt1UUiKR3lZZrEC/Tj1k4glpbC8Gw\u003d\u003d","answers":["in","about","of","with"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"BiEblYZ43PqrG82wdHo1wkuCgldccYVprJxQd9ESqY+ZsJwp2EXr3HZAIFJNSsDPHJ6/5YsWICz1W4Qm6tw0r6+CrMFZc7/5axYT0zCL+AW0iSstnEF/HvUXKwNfroVCT5BXzfnWYCn/m9sIAonxHcEh3086gOqBQjcAcLXILsdvzVcVOoVJG4QZ1/DVTnFR3HKoOT4vIRFtl/Arwbgja2w9uJob+bckVIomPWbxfBc0Xdk9k7Q1TO+FMwaEy38RFpCi2nPYHpgX2hE37qHhik6kZpOtU7XA24jHMT8cy8l8gTz79TWS9YWBqMa84fI2G3qjq1aHEvCflj6wBV55GbbE3p3Q3dZ00RT++0N2+Q0RhNpw5S23No4qjBYXyk10+dOz8nwD+fHNH7Mk3002iJrhp8dnGD3b9SYEfTt/mgHjg42yo5v/CU8XBgKEGBkZZxNkHdekVb2OZ68qiMitSZfZiCIPW+uRtGPaYyQbrLnWTq7S1eJxqKplD0xWM6PJB4hjzr14qdQVvkYpxWN5Ki9OMxoPUxykHI4q01rmqyvSeGOd0OCAQ2SsIzp1d9UnIIw31OrhjIFaXwtre4BXHTMjTdS8E5MQkvRiulXLr5bKM8QvZeTkRyNR6NOEZ3GM0MhP8oPsDv74U6ueeuLIkYjnRA5pYL84RrYF2d6AuuTc5b9O6bgMFDsPtxwTA3/DxsolzbTlVbn7NPq6QWR65AdDp4Ct/F4n8hoTOHXsG01QmevUMRgfe4fO5rBGj/IlRVfZqXq9y+FVnrBGWUorLoxIfengdEKeD+zEAF6Mzb5BoSGWUsi5jIP8LyWHxN9jghK5bedkPpuR2vhYnpvTF2oxp0HbljrTXnlA2irWWAQjKOG97APERooU8Ml5NkmsJroGRL43quGn6bmlbNODbQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7036","langCode":"en","question":"LlG5lM6o80ke0WnGthN+O9EWKbPR/oLI6nY85t8JT6dhZbdeZqQzD7hkxZXetYYwqjZm76jVDbFh+eW6o7e2AlOjeGML1msUiFJ3kXQTNIs\u003d","answers":["between","at","toward","during"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"X62FBBzQR30/ot4yI4eOpVeuaAtZOw52IJeI5tvUIAoqtU3FNlmRffYi7hQ7Ky8gepo8xiIPbAv3FDem6ERxelL9Lk/WzP4zzoXMWcOiFliEJPrL3o55DnxrwCc0nrRRUK12v560waoUKivveiyB7yn4jTaVyXEUg3Nn2JISJymR0JGH7lr51KGP/F7ogNJ70Tk2Kxmf/WLE0aJ3Hedci75uV09e4laP5iCK6TGzJfovpUCQXRKj8GKvAArzNeNynlEjhwvTjFdkcmCSbPokSkEK6TOhurhEQEea/db502oIBVeeNCH7Yw6AwwXCf6r2GtXU1qPVmOWsDiy8hkMCpAfUmgKXHNKzcZse+M89UHmml01sg8UazGkdGAD8/vylEui2qHtnWnicmqS5I33RpXVskrUiL1XNr5x8LlxHtQYxQoK81w8QPWbP6rLHqDY2q75kFD9xSwfHjXhiVO/OW+01Pvwxt6jm4sijFwNNXoPzBjNwcJt9JzwxoDQi6A+q4M6qIMl6cmIJ4fOwoD76wrZv3OFSMSC5WjVsPV6Ty4Vxy7P203SVs5OnGqI4nI3tKwB9oCah6CHoPT2O5UcpZJdYGMr5/MpA0BJYPjhwN0YpcAPDgsao97IXsrGt42kQWsfgzXZxlAvi+IjFCrZlZwC6DlERagl6ttncJQfIj77sLcQug8SjwdRaWMCoa+Zkmf3T7jwtdxwzZ2a2+1fog/fWBYVb5Gr4Bkv2T7NuKAxwrLbB3re2TFBHtGcwnu70sw/lE/0BgTVsr9aK7vfCi7INJFye63CTEwArGz1elWo\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7037","langCode":"en","question":"D7vxnWhsYbLbwPzbPFuXtgHHkRv3mexOZVZ399m/dYQyz07PUSULMhDQ8bOyvDyqk31IxNcDUfOr76VZH/VTG/WoXhQwwQozXD6lnfQjY/A\u003d","answers":["about","by","with ","from "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"Bijrx7IRP71CyDChJa48m4azS1Xu5xI23ipAIv3HhvOv4BiSYlFCoo47c2zegnunjULNmvI8S1Pldv+gds/Oi6TermlTUptQyz8HewVcCx30zpaQCgiK6ufKSxbYV16j3rhUDbkbO22oEwB9p7vrE+0+pEAniG3XsbY5xF7F11ekJCqQOoElD+b5JRCTMWpS/ZYTbL3XuQvsZD06W0sX8zrL8pHMNBH2y9EU7FS+jzH7LtXG9NBMLGULB2BGaDEH4pBO3lamnvSu2fzbHAX2NlgRN7xFF/kruAZhAkjSSMhiYaAxhnIHaUfwlv2iOGVOw0K07mXitK5KsMvXXDeFIGa5suLUAkQaCiQHkqYdqoinf6GtoI/yFiPh/vqDT0qeDUMa5MRowQD94KAqM68YgUTu79Kl3tuKTCvh4xqeXHMG24y3zARsGwcP/DwueXGFg5okQ4P5KHOCO5zyPDKJYYdYPlJEa1oqT8pySj0kHjlyUtic7QE4/3h0CnjmXvJgZthZMWBrWz+0FszQkgOSeM5EDQxFMzTvRoDuQYNmjYKyz/aqLzuEuUm0BiAIE0Hl+y0+QGRZbXoQtRNSutuvZvJh7dCur92FI8ChUMM7YyeOM07zOtkslqe5qxl3YOW94doVK3alC2AWQrlgoeNLzQWyeET9qjYTv3L/XlqgK9mzD+UT/QGBNWyv1oru98KL3bcD8Lsz4IdIpGStboBgxIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7038","langCode":"en","question":"5SWRYhEP07OUt4ssGjs377TmLmsWptnKNbqLdbHZ1JK2Xyo/KxXLqvs5kchT77HgbU5G05RXPoLfCVIytWLQkXX2c5SGI7Us2FnlnsbEaa5w1Fo2o/goldXcyvGPZfmD","answers":["of","about","for","by"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"O8ppYWgXDWP75ISyBmd9oAZoh6Knv4Nh1215SGKLoJawm6EFw/Uw2i68WevEoF7YLgb+opSrfcaMh4CGGR1hgzTjIsCUQ1HNAC05cXBguclpB7HPnrHnwveN7SFJQBIoqLkp9PCRRBFE/0rAtseh6SBhPdwKQ3rtyOkNI5EG0ZBidHG4hTwo/wCgF2NEJkZYOHKeiyzbqEJQZLgZWeLRHh/yX80MLr4N4f4bIh2nZSZXzQyR6pPVPpVjAv9K3vSrIewBRT43xgKleh2JIkCfEtEkdrv5N9+YGGId1up+yTtG2I7/sez1eVBHyGQ5hV9cJGS6G8PboxPhLlh6eQglGR5Ah5snyar0pSPOND4dNP9wbmQltCzP7D+SdGmDoGEHKRzQAKw9YRF/TlUGjSoWc77GtJml4oYXAi0/0GJzwHQaLzpQAIbZN8tGLhhc3YYDhN8innpXVryHqWH9hb6N85DfBy6nELSdNoKIOic8yxLyMMxlt3NmnpDaOBFk09zKEKctazX6PdMEULul0vAP2zXyLlfqroctfyNfgj1ndUssBPZ1WP9P5aRlck4I232EZ+Fp2FKdnsWKE7d05JO0lFCL/e9u55hojCCj/PJTavKyfTZRMlTW0SE/pb4GQwcbM/xkueY89UMqid7FjVIaMCtucRmL8f3LBxor5Uf8aTFA2qz82htPx96yd2oPaLhggFaqphTeH9a6i4nL82vx/RshxoJjxMLaJ1Q+aOI/Juk\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7039","langCode":"en","question":"ZTJlH5xWwq125k5FR4Kz5I2d8g1JJkKfJfhm2QFptJT0Lr3TbXnN8Tp7nLWg7GPlGSWVgwdV5VNaTWKbNDwSzQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["of","on","about ","in"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"m9WtPvps0luXdmhlom5DpPw/OeVwcxI2iorSDVF1O9XVjiA/o5s7lnAtKhQsn4ktOxdq4YPQltstoIhs3AZy0wXt20aIyj1LkBSK6pG1PvEQgPgeMRubNnV7R+qdteUtSlsEIL0X73620+bdTA3y0ILOAU2Jiuwn2RCIudB3JfLjLTOyG+snihhSH6MKDnggFgqUkmA5FGWg2hqmTzIwoLOgAwuX6ktTkJPycraLRfeQuOta+kKfK0homLPNnd96RdLiAyzdLOIeIIIe5cBKD12RcUBCazb1478xBz4CpbKkoqBhkPLVOfX8NUh5jw8OA/sSzKpXSyGUuAOV+VXtnO7Y2zCB+lM7f3GAv4jNRAsPLXn9YB+aS8XXXE7WV/Pvx97Ksvr0yQikIeClaWU98fWzAssQzUE+bE/UY+1Cwnxh2wW+ePKROeqn29Tr1tpsxpbO3ci9sSDx06YEPwIR36r5TwSdDZR1Td7Tbu7f3jy/y8oVZo7a34fHWKVuoRqpGi5kNdU4hXx6ypx+pUv/RZk47toJUV+MvXnbv6Frvxexotuv8SzOrf7EeImCOJO1PyIJHruiTq5qpmd0o6/GenwKOGtITVQm3URAKDMKZFwEDiYy8jKmkb3G+ZVCDp+RyRGcag0e2XtQt2/dySNPA1jdZu2QPaQX6ooPNwetwW+mTf7Y+iCaldI0Nwx0oDxaFJv3UFA7p8LcF2BsidmZDdKHRxZtZ0dxviwVhBpfvAkynqA4qa0+k5rrLzPDG3PGjdxhp8Awnrf2aFvbrt+c2VnemjTdrnzdaxY3BvUQK9Rlp0TOMnGUmZWN/t8LK1L4zC5yoK0P/iFyKSMm9X2PUOS3JX63eRjwwVbbLe0KSp+js3NtnbZzW6BH9WyWQUk0MDDoJs2R3TPvxQwNB/Ik2HzAzKvTBOXdiX6jiTdAcwx223hssYnDldix7vdt5T56J5olLwWgGTJE1pQLzgp1QaOYgGokS4CzrFTsdENl2CZkf7bbjUhYW10OKa0KtG87uxEStpcsXhyW7baGKwNX91r1LYLVY18sDyzBstM9RomS+3Wppv8lxAWOMHcQs4bffJc3baDhSgP62RSDgKyPpHISgVuQX1pVuvnMvY9HcWeIXwuqB22uPu4lIXgbZHeFJnsBtoc9XGXM/fpG7bzZE/SQPqDHqato25D7AHNq8vY1F++UCYaNZXzW6rOBGNghWDGfatJQBSMhBx6JsLQj0QzPMJ2HoMKwWBdxiCX5c4s\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7040","langCode":"en","question":"7WV3x87rBgAjfeuVxDzCNUX2ZG0MV6W9HY9uOl4YmmhxMK6jZCLzi5UKpqp/yscEnWP2fRs5KKuS56TIacVnHg\u003d\u003d","answers":["on","for","at","inside"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"6AiWSJTulsO2oZBaFqNnXfPIARYiUiDh1b7skjSbbvh/PD7/sgKFwHXiYtEmWrisordRxoPAsuDlGpcxAU1gM83gyeevI4RyBXlsaH56qIQg7azdixJrwfhM+FUWnsMuj4flOxo/3rgG9JaM4BSHwc9yTOKEoF8Jy32mp51Qh3Tx3U8OzXSX2WeqQT9CFCQ+o+ZVmbGFCEzBThqK0YYFifRz2s3JOgpPdjiARA7OTkHsiMhTcttO66cXw1I9XkxKfDBSWNKxCNeW0zg1jgWka/HxDhcNsoQRM/w4qSi7dbbDL39dBBC3mF8hHKoacW5dUCJ92UUH5h2P2fhAj/C6DBYKlJJgORRloNoapk8yMKCzoAMLl+pLU5CT8nK2i0X3kLjrWvpCnytIaJizzZ3fekXS4gMs3SziHiCCHuXASg9dkXFAQms29eO/MQc+AqWypKKgYZDy1Tn1/DVIeY8PDgP7EsyqV0shlLgDlflV7Zzu2NswgfpTO39xgL+IzUQLDy15/WAfmkvF11xO1lfz78feyrL69MkIpCHgpWllPfH1swLLEM1BPmxP1GPtQsJ8YdsFvnjykTnqp9vU69babMaWzt3IvbEg8dOmBD8CEd+q+U8EnQ2UdU3e027u3948v8vKFWaO2t+Hx1ilbqEaqRouZDXVOIV8esqcfqVL/0WZOO7aCVFfjL1527+ha78XsaLbr/Eszq3+xHiJgjiTtT8iCR67ok6uaqZndKOvxnpDSX8H7xjDi27+SO9AlGvhndq5iefsoUAe/JwOEvIO6WWrtBqIi9zlihZLKf7x74r0CZ6TQrZDTaFbsD4BslSNRNrtxZBjaNxENGDrN+24IZaKGLZY8sCy2/T8bO5K01Bi1KHiJc9yKnChp3k5G1pV760bA7CbIx9cuSi1J868/Eg5SZpmUDx6h8UC/G1DTfPKYox1mMjdSzc5sle5v2SQkvsMRIjErEDHvhWzSWAUqeSWWNRTW3Y5z0jBHjdqD4g\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7041","langCode":"en","question":"s8CnI6PVqX9E3Ui4aj+d1oRngl87NxTrxoXXZybm39T+jF1+vfGt1ouFCyWr7+h10vJ5fi1AHDQStp01BI9fAFZ2HjQJrt7Yja0y/fDtxCM\u003d","answers":["about","by","with ","from"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"wrc399oDqjPpxCM4CocSNseaT0EVLjml32lpEiJPJIA1PKaDXW9/hqlBKDSsjtTa3rhUDbkbO22oEwB9p7vrE6FAs10qEwRmm+shM8P7glV82GqJroVtuoHKn/GWTd1eJSob3CQE5G1wzjxnwwWO/Rpt83vjolaCmih43+cUQysDzhwNYTPfcRDImlz3Iz02dCfd9Wss3CFwdjgQpCjz2WazsY1si+mQ3PTCaJnyurDSiEc+GIWAIYscHoLTRROPTB362UR9KC7omepaZZ1ixn6q7MrX64ohHPsOjlNpz35UlpxSoNPqnqel4c0FTTOobHkHloGDZIX30k/nOraY1QjRi1gPdmhrS/TFruyPh6jXh6cJDiczx+G/NA9uR2VOGrbdNiItquhEJMnERIg5ISYkew6awZr+qzn4nhQWT8+2E19sxfMZbTAxQHZYgOxpsGhyegUK2hDADqgsPJ+0pMaAjubYMCgiUfPNEpsbaYFiIpXjEUM2FoeP+9hJk58uABgR+tvW+GZbcVmmQ3PJjmwt3wijvYPEVm5NrX/ScXNHRF2XKYV6sFXN8wML069QxyfqrEz5zefSDl1NjsWWGb/oUhDJP+Q/ArvD0TQDCvDRF9XbRlOKIuT4+YhaHKqFDnPYTCjVKG+/5TLgFwXmATeIf3erXrTk8eBxyZJjLmVYMZ9q0lAFIyEHHomwtCPRT/NdoOLw0LzdLW3lvtkbXQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7042","langCode":"en","question":"ohe/9/3bDjpBD3VJGLGmnFyUxKnaoF78pico7R8BAszSIjXhourWkbEWT8f/3DX4vBgKXfL2uSZelhJq9PuO2Vx60VYqw8MvZmGT6jxVJFE\u003d","answers":["behind","of","to","among"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"zXzPKY0N+kx0u5efTpWWLI9ECELGO8F5AButheH+qTM347tfLy+D6Oaf3LMWD0wzzAHMra2P1xu/yisJ91OFAnf9Dev2dWQE9+9e+sINLA6PW6Sbga/JM25fsEIYGEm5DLgQ2M1pxXqFaf0PoHckXvSEVdrZhn9VQe9m3o0zOMiGo98ylC80bZ6CWdoGHuZv3NvrYqJB90kB9eTZ0N5puMqt/57Q6X/Yu+zVqyWEZgG/AFjvhW62eTnabidAdPE4897g4N8TjK0bJizb9ZTye86QdmyIw24kZEnsy38yBg2ZvNg+rHQmeWOs6/KAk/4lKrLo++AUrCPxHyVv8OVMHZUx3CfywTgF691LdUpMTppsPbiaG/m3JFSKJj1m8XwXNF3ZPZO0NUzvhTMGhMt/ERaQotpz2B6YF9oRN+6h4YpOpGaTrVO1wNuIxzE/HMvJfIE8+/U1kvWFgajGvOHyNht6o6tWhxLwn5Y+sAVeeRm2xN6d0N3WdNEU/vtDdvkNm7aXpEGaTHHHwixvREuUoKvFZsJSt46tHTe/oanmjUJaUoNMcZaEDlU+3n+WBlhU7LMyFoE7GykYCE8LLZK6R4QB8kv7z/gfxXak/xoTa3Vu21UlWlDnHEp+oYh00JVP+P/LrABB02/hJiCqYXCe2LMP5RP9AYE1bK/Wiu73wotHujiJcCLPq6h843CGFWaG"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7043","langCode":"en","question":"a/KJfH4qWBYKIzkWyAbErOPEqmObV5OVkdL6GGqBnVCEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["for","along","into","outside"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"O8ppYWgXDWP75ISyBmd9oAZoh6Knv4Nh1215SGKLoJawm6EFw/Uw2i68WevEoF7YLgb+opSrfcaMh4CGGR1hgzTjIsCUQ1HNAC05cXBguclpB7HPnrHnwveN7SFJQBIoqLkp9PCRRBFE/0rAtseh6SBhPdwKQ3rtyOkNI5EG0ZBidHG4hTwo/wCgF2NEJkZYOHKeiyzbqEJQZLgZWeLRHj+YVmlvJ/5g2El1+cdoQic0N1MtI2A3bF7ioivParVsUKPB7sOISXr+NX2OSGallluVaGxylZUO8Ht7hFPz1Pxth798PUa8wIv7I5Badc8WhdB+JvvOMR/zgrM8B5VavEmKzFGozBT90+IIkdNsfzofyzP4mh1Ac8FlXUC4moX2EXrN5uQybknOLKs7iP5fwDUsD2Ipys+557+CFIZs6t0HUL0HgO/sJC2qHzrrEGPi+SvJ6EeNXiqDkvGFFt7HgJ8FWOaVkCTXeRyzJcVOrudMW9tMO2icddojjPxVdvuwqjLfbx1znNk1Gc5vyQRgepTGx1D+OmAjDhLfhwDcBsXN6NtC/EYlIwJCn7NxXsXsbi8TUWs8kEISOE7JYWyXCVQ/nTFkoKsTQFE77v92gTITqCJX3kO+7C8vOuPupcF5RMSi11w5Wsz3nOHue04cK4e3hzaraH8XY+lAlOU5wPgOqTJO2hPBiPtHo/WQsULmQ8Z4oJm2TxfdlS52CfVEMw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7044","langCode":"en","question":"BLfvLCYgyV0cQrQfiUmVfoMStWzVvrHgFUKYHR7owm7MsWZLASMi5mL2Wf4XbRAXn6TCOrA00dUAG7L86zN8/BcpfAI/6Gm0NM9AZAydumbH4PYhjmFTft+Zh/63D1+QVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["in","to","with","about"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"vApVJreBPHppbZ13TrxqmfydCRR40Q67Zz/kYXeU8CHMR9vbJOF7x4n8er3ftKCF92Bk3BEQozGhXSCjRxpUSd4+Yb76+RpEprF9yOsxAGKh+H3YQrV003gQkSMHub0xfRBqYzudCNta1VLvIpTCX9OYd663iy3OXxXO1qBGktvj0bsH8EZJSfn8JCZUMxBVBA4+JpsFpwhCM9s46YN4pZlUsJeCHNbc5g4kCPi49HPyGXbhazXuXmOA94njqupLxEwxQS24JrUT8mO4DKs9ZnoZTgxGSomUgjrg5cuYv6Tbg5fN570Ixv1qyGQcu83CqS9ZpYSY9jNXJikT8gFadg5y0SmvcK3armNv7DBmPvX507PyfAP58c0fsyTfTTaImuGnx2cYPdv1JgR9O3+aAeODjbKjm/8JTxcGAoQYGRlnE2Qd16RVvY5nryqIyK1Jl9mIIg9b65G0Y9pjJBusudZOrtLV4nGoqmUPTFYzo8kHiGPOvXip1BW+RinFY3kqL04zGg9THKQcjirTWuarK9J4Y53Q4IBDZKwjOnV31ScgjDfU6uGMgVpfC2t7gFcdMyNN1LwTkxCS9GK6VcuvlsozxC9l5ORHI1Ho04RncYzQyE/yg+wO/vhTq5564siRiOdEDmlgvzhGtgXZ3oC65Nzlv07puAwUOw+3HBMDf8PGyiXNtOVVufs0+rpBZHrkQ76XtLN/fvMIUh+BalK/Knzx78TQ5hMZXrfGJuv69ajmA6LN/vjhK5csSemcELYreV4g5rrzbj+TZzXCx7uQ9uvU8beCzkLJgcyJFFNU7/PhjyfdnLRSd0NXa0dofjvEFrM9u6T8tGSPexzHA5Ky19IUys5cLjWQUZZTO+OCjlNSBVJ5oDNTnfDZDP2W2AaJUO1aQCTmixzdAdQPkg0jG9Eyftrb2kDvGJ5fr8rJ0nXSGtDpPAobmCmYMGFQmMYslGqyw4h7l0iSC2nUTVsDnCMo4b3sA8RGihTwyXk2SawiyLXaM+LnxS16t32MJKsk"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7045","langCode":"en","question":"DupTJj8PkS2zdnZhviHhLUtKod6w3HjRD2SEMDjVdu/Z1m1CF3ol7b1iT1hTgIvn","answers":["among","during ","with","between "],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"X62FBBzQR30/ot4yI4eOpVeuaAtZOw52IJeI5tvUIAoqtU3FNlmRffYi7hQ7Ky8gepo8xiIPbAv3FDem6ERxelL9Lk/WzP4zzoXMWcOiFliEJPrL3o55DnxrwCc0nrRRUK12v560waoUKivveiyB7yn4jTaVyXEUg3Nn2JISJymM3VpwkS3D6gevhZ1VFiyA+SOZuhaCs5KtPp6cqnfWleB98W6psspA/Pl4XuD+yx7ZT4PgFo0I5v5BVssxiWiUYvvOMuJQSx4oV0cg1u1WOqtHGHgKh29OFW8pOcTeQYzyC1Sp9E5PCQqcFFkB4neVy/PN4AwzvaPwLldAlhJ3DuOgN+TEtAO55WCvDqK64fnf9F+39l13guNCEEevmeeQKnrkrl2B6Ws0De/NtrpVSuRNVXPKTgHiiMd05HsVxSGH2ftH9GunXaLwzPLxNdxDdJ7NcdWbXmo+l4/MGzYSYzIUVu0WMLUaBhnTakLLwVrnJUE8jp/wS95qfZjeqPrVxo5MMNDXGl8fQeo8uLdD4fm/W9WB7Fn55XOOaxhZlYNb38QTagIu1xdRiLnsTvmr3jJ3F+o9+HAJz9kejerLsSPjknM63mkgb6Q5/HaIsuYOWCeNKEBNK9AmPGe90kc+BIT/1GOdjhpuxdd9jVYiYI6WndqktXHpKWRlKr+bT5zTAKlpUhgxZ4d37cCMc+tD"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7046","langCode":"en","question":"TGIbieZrJvjf8QloQvExoSEEBhBelXudfZShMmlm4TNqrxX+wTlbf3eaRwSIC/9htIxbLiauwsbkMJQzCssIbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["with","from","by","about"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"wrc399oDqjPpxCM4CocSNseaT0EVLjml32lpEiJPJIA1PKaDXW9/hqlBKDSsjtTa3rhUDbkbO22oEwB9p7vrE6FAs10qEwRmm+shM8P7glV82GqJroVtuoHKn/GWTd1eJSob3CQE5G1wzjxnwwWO/Rpt83vjolaCmih43+cUQysDzhwNYTPfcRDImlz3Iz02dCfd9Wss3CFwdjgQpCjz2WazsY1si+mQ3PTCaJnyurDSiEc+GIWAIYscHoLTRROPTB362UR9KC7omepaZZ1ixn6q7MrX64ohHPsOjlNpz35UlpxSoNPqnqel4c0FTTOobHkHloGDZIX30k/nOraY1QjRi1gPdmhrS/TFruyPh6jXh6cJDiczx+G/NA9uR2VOGrbdNiItquhEJMnERIg5ISYkew6awZr+qzn4nhQWT8+2E19sxfMZbTAxQHZYgOxpsGhyegUK2hDADqgsPJ+0pMaAjubYMCgiUfPNEpsbaYFiIpXjEUM2FoeP+9hJk58uABgR+tvW+GZbcVmmQ3PJjmwt3wijvYPEVm5NrX/ScXO0zqbrV/zEFw8xxV6wiOaJnERBtSvOcGmP8K8TJKCaUYBcAuciKmnBLgQNUrPjXI780f0JiS8NN4AlKI2TJN//QNqs/NobT8fesndqD2i4YIBWqqYU3h/WuouJy/Nr8f134dFcHSFDOoHfWgwrpfFE"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7047","langCode":"en","question":"iTqmdKKFnxiei+ov94lF4Ff/jzKCIscMZHov8BW1h9o9QMKaVUV0z2zSv65VSfx4","answers":["for","by","with","of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"6AiWSJTulsO2oZBaFqNnXfPIARYiUiDh1b7skjSbbvh/PD7/sgKFwHXiYtEmWrisbhLDoN5CyyY/JBudwEhEswfUmgKXHNKzcZse+M89UHmNRHXPScGrNXBCTYehDQ1OayXvJKxcFOrAhIs2TF6RfUvHOPbnNPXlswVQdo5bZ+XhZlmB1JB6l2PYWzziZTTtcWvQAAKh0LOmd+QiB+q4QP4gES2X2/HZhLj+2TEt0IlzrjwVD3FKEa6DZOXqS3A2rRNpVvp2+ULSWYwZROWrsQjovhwGjx9nGDmjPOAYt4t1rzUhnS9/eXKKdHlreDe+EHxdIwmvyQ1Dsb0IZF4xRsePhc8/kCc9Vo+JbNEZNCC6lThHWIM+NliW/KPW22aKL+szqTGuaokHn8cMWInLuNeHpwkOJzPH4b80D25HZU4att02Ii2q6EQkycREiDkhJiR7DprBmv6rOfieFBZPz7YTX2zF8xltMDFAdliA7GmwaHJ6BQraEMAOqCw8n7SkPdfuQ0WafEpC+98f7O4i+mcODUtudl7sasooh4OJPDDhqA6DztHkIHsH0oqeYUL+YMKBBwNtJ0iOLnzlvPYgy1bmPpclv6m8Tov87KE5ienZkMXwZYEUAV6xjH/UcfsKX7h5G5lWY+TS7utjL41ri+bNKMQVFUXGvcazFzqm3IrsbqHnVOZP5sgd29hgomfNo55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7048","langCode":"en","question":"2Iz75YL+El6fRBwt+QVpqcfh4qQrh5i6pjXHJIiVpvcODNBSi5aMCJS3rTaObSL9WN3fMGRTx9bzVaSoCh1fQuOsbYtEFsZXlmZ/i3l+YNM\u003d","answers":["by","since","at","against"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"FEAa/TPOBKxiSy89lZghQwdoZxjx1QZqYS1+DPOoaCb6y2CcVvmtxA+bcxfrCrt0vu1cS0vOtOBMNx+6qXhbi0P67kdwTD4U/D4HwQrQGv9udCMsOGYIH/SZNUxZhjJUthXRme2T2tAlQ/Fq+QIT90iuCjqUZvb2x5Ze6zle3lALw19LuJbSsUtK4XHswIEBjG8W70dAjkkhGoVtoAyrpi/awb/BPvRJFkfS53lhCjx8MlX58Rm2jYDIReAApOKa54tydhM5QreRwF2sQfrluZAZoZNqQ9z4Tx9u0zszH/FGKO/acta51YiGTLDkdMSLEVbIgIiSCnoFb74qoL0isDnlo6/vtDiB1PExmPkHxOxUCR8554GfhN+U7ZddDx2y1G+pHQ1ZxxjJxqMArjE+oGeuiNugcEa72V3ZmgpARx7BEc3C9MOoy/5b/5+W+PUc1bnlB8P62uxgc/oZ8livX+vzTG3O54pcsh54EKRyfs/Iqc8WJ31ZZ3t3/kHCp6pao9PILQmP/9RunWVYnSK1q/qjXfqvdvePTWuV7VFstE1TP6GfdY2GhaSTrduEgjjgb4apm2G4LesZ4BpmmX7UWmazsY1si+mQ3PTCaJnyurDSiEc+GIWAIYscHoLTRROPTB362UR9KC7omepaZZ1ixgcpEUXhU8kkpB1wf9isd+oqMNCX8xtvcNjEmGGZig455/hmATvkPeblSDXAJxeseYVkQViYB2RBcFPl1BvWpibytyAF/FYw84pPfT7nNmOP2QdKsKMdZlZIT7KxFZYPfeRWQbB2A5XAi3TViHxLQsgDRxSPApDiBUMmWltYgI1m9rugCU9M+x1Jc5dVunhN3+lsbSEGNN8EyeAt2z4C3uMpxAqc6Bj1/KfRLdnulV09uWFsTZIfBa62rQx+TRYCHMSxFAVtQmnAebpWCh7jFPv6+OQ5tqYAYJWWIs/GYygr"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7049","langCode":"en","question":"jCZpefyKfbZNcp4+4ULh2IgSaWiY4Tfz3mzmgmGn3TsVwLpcYNNJ/FOFuIoigEcNNoXtMooLDWpip2UHMsEAVA\u003d\u003d","answers":["with ","at ","after","among"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"Es15p0wqWvHqNtb/OLWsRNdndwwzSl0gJqwtWYn4iAMLrwnIEUUirDsHOCY2xHxGc1k62q+RukhOCBOG80D6Vchnzs0ani4drambS+x7eb7d3ooJSIRySoemm+NmVGvHx35FShcXxX/mHNHVbYGlFSwRdLJeqlEd60LOFsXPGu8BlNsrxVWB2WcVq4WXHnMy+YF+0h6Yv4gyCaroDof9f4wlaM5fsv34n4HbxRsTbwM16wFOBs6Zw8i1xRG5CTCo4zntPY2lQLFcyn2+de7IuHUDW6ctA9aoZSXoYR/vDvtCpUNbQ+dnuR5tGUBUIjpHI3umWs4z4tTsL2+XVkm5DXUDW6ctA9aoZSXoYR/vDvtWxDb2acscIpB08w38b5M1OIrQ8FOkqy86caCj6JPvZS1/sOgFCC0e5DbeJbqdsbO5Q3ebHlHGAQI/2nUc0O7oTwdX/T8T5eLpLXR0SqscyKIkk+Gwf5D0V+T9XJApbKqTw/AhMCN8Ll5R4+gDBNKi7BDMWa4emdGD1GbPC4u1eDMzPxvtALxA9MlLSxp++7v7vGRHMw6AF63Ii5X9gHAYpvN/DsmUp5LnWtWfbo/qNaSdCjCeF8r8ZXC9yBjWhOCq8pnfm5RQLizYNBbItIN4CXZFhR6VPTfvmkgmdl4ozjL0uhjrT8VkqMZjanYK8wSUSeMIBZHm9O6N9PCJs/cVIyjhvewDxEaKFPDJeTZJrAofPz5YO1RDWPfxIMmYpoo\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7050","langCode":"en","question":"YOCJn95bw2LjNn294wlJhqFYQsCIG1lhZ0o2odg/6VbNc8+lQ2ESihnL06Hv5gfs3EX+Ia5gkEtL4bLZMwfehA\u003d\u003d","answers":["since ","at","by","in"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"Zuw9XipiFvsCiutiuKLogpXR4M/KxxjyggTVjjRHoGOc9AEsrVwFpxw8CO0Pu3rKi4wATSPEVIiaJLjjcNwXzmk9UUjOt+jpgb2OFAiQJJ01AbjuE5Ud7+Pi2Nq8hcfefRfsZqc0pykv/6ZQn903vPnyf9tt9SNsrsCbRb2FWSLiSNNvWcsXD8s5tXpE+YNCykKPK8hyfONtOILxd/zDS7B1IO3k5CYplq4HehR6CNTGFyUo1aYY90w3txQola4yI+uC4x4jfoO1Ybt+SNkruhqxJP56P7PMv4ekItGvV83oF85nAuObk9apwgspr41+bXaNpVF/8uk7raFIU4HEOUDhnJw1x6WViYjLDrYbDu1qhkm0xNC1c9BcA73xtuZRYBE+9d0v6Ll8lvMKIT4ndMpzXcf6dMMWXmThQrV14Q8zaFqgjeTOOnZrzxjeMaNl6Nl0QjowtYqQagam2wZEXkq6CZQcwjt+wN8iArNnZqcQO8aYr5RxmF33PwN7na68ZFvQDAa5OQnXlPwzWCeGgPTfFcSiKwzblLyjcla+glCywSnPGdSG4JDKiBxgMIxnMsceewCK3kQVu8aZeVPKqRDl/AiYS1GXf7J3n7jBg/Wc9yraYZ3+Yes0Rr31Lq6/8m11PKiEqxKKrCulyePG/0NpBsCwtlcGkaj6gcD4DWPlM2VldL/cPy0AqCDonH+ULBpupT/fjR6QEmI7mtpbfW6nPQD0pvKnbqdo4/P4s9FblnW7CHRS5Yakl3yrHJIZHH9Mhl0km8VQo3ReToYAeIkFg77+p2+nXNiWHpTXZrICs+QsrE/Zk8CbW7BqD+YQtd6TYMmxSW9nnqTQRzfJuhQMPza4bs/h7ydvmisN+12EQkf3OwoQJ4Ao2Y0nLFQKt3WstnCkvfRF1hgNhXpM2zVCJa3o681QGQBUGxFczfKzD+UT/QGBNWyv1oru98KLdadc6//BSKYEfVFP4CIxEg\u003d\u003d"}]